<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GetNotified</string>
    <string name="haleem">چکن بون لیس(اُبلا ہوا) ۲۰۰ گرام\n
دال ماش، \nمونگ، \nمسور،\n چنا ۵۰، ۵۰ گرام\n
چاول ۵۰ گرام\n
گندم کے دانے ۵۰ گرام\n
ادرک لہسن کا پیسٹ ڈیڑھ چائے کے چمچ\n
ہری مرچ چار عدد\n
نمک حسبِ ذائقہ\n
لال مرچ پیسی ہوئی دو کھانے کے چمچ\n
سفید زیرہ پیسا ہوا ڈیڑھ چائے کے چمچ\n
؂دھنیا پیسا ہوا ڈیڑھ چائے کے چمچ\n
ہلدی ڈیڑھ چائے کے چمچ\n
پانی حسبِ ضرورت\n
پیاز ایک عدد\n
تازہ لیموں کا رس ایک چوتھائی کپ\n
آئل آدھا کپ\n
سفید زیرہ ثابت آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n\n
\nمُرغ حلیم ترکیب\n
\nدال چنا،مونگ، مسور،ماش ،چاول،گندم کے دانے کو ایک گھنٹہ پانی میں بھیگو کر رکھ دیں۔بھیگی ہوئی دالیں، چاول، گندم کو پانی میں ڈال کر جھاگ آنے تک اُبال لیں۔جھاگ اُتار کر نمک، ہلدی ڈال کر پندرہ سے بیس منٹ تک اُبال کر بلینڈر میں پیس لیں۔بونلیس چکن کو اُبال کر چھوٹے چھو ٹے ریشے کر لیں۔پکانے والے برتن میںآئل، پیاز،سفید زیرہ ثابت ڈال کر لائٹ براوٗن ہونے تک فرائی کرلیں۔اب ہری مرچ کٹی ہوئی، ادرک لہسن کا پیسٹ، نمک،سفید زیرہ پیسا ہوا، دھنیا پیسا ہوا، چکن کے ریشے،پیسی ہوئی دالیں،چاول، گندم کا پیسٹ ڈال لیں۔ لیمو ں کا رس ڈال کر چار سے پانچ منٹ تک پکایں۔آپکا مزے دار مُرغ حلیم تیار ہے۔\n\n
گارنش(ادرک، لیموں، براؤن پیاز، ہری مرچ)\n\n

پکا نے کا وقت :1 گھنٹہ 30منٹ
</string>
    <string name="hareesa">دال مونگ دوسو گرام\n
دال مسور دوسو گرام\n
دال ماش دوسو گرام\n
دال چنا دوسو گرام\n
پانی حسبِ ضرورت\n
دلیہ ایک سو گرام\n
چاول ایک سو گرام\n
کھانے کا تیل تین کھانے کے چمچ\n
پیاز تین عدد\n
سبز مرچ چھ عدد\n
بڑی اِلائچی تین عدد\n
دار چینی تین عدد\n
اُبلا ہو ا گوشت پانچ سو گرام\n
نمک حسبِ ذائقہ\n
لال مرچ پاؤڈر ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
یخنی ایک کپ\n
ادرک پیسٹ ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
سبز مرچ ،ادرک ،براؤن پیاز (گارنش )\n
\n\nترکیب
۔ایک برتن تمام دالیں، دلیہ اور چاول ڈال کر دو گھنٹے کے لیے بھِگوکر رکھ دیں ۔\n
۔اب ایک پین میں کھانے کا تیل لیں اور اس میں پیاز سلائس کٹنگ ڈال کر لائٹ براؤن کر لیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں سبز مرچ ،بڑی اِلائچی ،دارچینی،ادرک پیسٹ ،گلا ہوا گوشت،نمک اور لال مرچ پاؤڈرڈال کرپانچ منٹ کے لیے بھونائی کر لیں ۔\n
۔اب ایک پین میں بھِگوئی ہوئی تمام دالیں ،دلیہ اور چاول ڈال کر اچھی طرح گلالیں اور گرائیند کر لیں ۔\n
۔اب گرائینڈ کی ہوئی دالوں کو بھُنے ہوئے گوشت میں ملالیں اوراس میں یخنی ڈال کر گاڑھا ہونے تک پکالیں ۔\n
۔اب اس پر سبز مرچ ،ادرک اور براؤن پیاز کی گارنش کر لیں ۔\n
آپکا مزیدار ہریسہ تیار ہے ۔\n
پکا نے کا وقت: چالیس منٹ\n
</string>
    <string name="chickenWhiteKarahi">	8عدد   K and Ns Seekh Kebab\n
\nآلو	4-5عدد \n
کھانے کا تیل \n
\nادرک لہسن پیسٹ	1کھانے کا چمچ \n
چِلی ساس 1چائے کا چمچ \n
پیپریکا\n	آدھا چائے کا چمچ       \n
نمک\n	حسبِ ذائقہ     \n
موزریلا چیز\n	1کپ
چیڈر چیز آدھا کپ  \n
دودھ\n	1چوتھائی کپ
مایونیز 2-3کھانے کے چمچ \n

\nترکیب:  \n
پیکٹ پر دی ہدایات کے مطابق K and Ns Seekh Kebabتیار  کر لیں اور آدھے کاٹ لیں۔     \n
اب آلوؤں کو لمبائی میں کاٹ کر دس منٹ کے لئے ٹھنڈے پانی میں بھگو دیں اور پھر آلوؤں کو کپڑے سے صاف کر کے ایک گھنٹے کے لئے فریج میں رکھ دیں۔  \n
پہلے آلوؤں کو ہلکا سا نمک لگائیں پھر ایک پین میں کھانے کا تیل گرم کر کے درمیانی آنچپرپانچ سے چھ منٹ کے لئے فرائز فرائی کر لیں اور باہر نکال کر دس منٹ کے لئے سائیڈ پر رکھ دیں۔    \n
اب پھر فرائز گولڈن براؤن ہونے تک فرائی کر لیں۔   \n
\nچیز ساس ترکیب: \n
ایک پین میں کھانے کا تیل گرم کر کے اس میں ادرک لہسن پیسٹ، چِلی ساس، نمک، پیپریکا، موزریلا، چیڈر چیز، دودھ اور مایونیز ڈال کر چیز پگھلنے دیں۔ اب ایک پلیٹر میں K and Ns Seekh Kebabرکھ کر اس پر چیز ڈالیں اور ہیلو پینو اور ہرا پیاز چھڑک دیں۔       \n
\nتیاری کا وقت : 10 منٹ \n
پکانے کا وقت : 20 منٹ</string>
    <string name="MurghMusallam">چکن میرینیشن:\n
ہول چکن	1عدد \n
نمک	1چائے کا چمچ \n
سرکہ	آدھا کپ \n
ادرک لہسن پیسٹ	1کھانے کا چمچ \n
دہی	3چوتھائی کپ \n
الائچی پاؤڈر	آدھا چائے کا چمچ \n
ہری مرچ پیسٹ	2چائے کے چمچ \n
دھنیا پاؤڈر	1کھانے کا چمچ \n
سرکہ	1کھانے کا چمچ \n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ \n
لال مرچ پاؤڈر	1چائے کا چمچ \n
ذیرہ پاؤڈر	1چائے کا چمچ \n
\nفلنگ اجزاء:
ابلے ہوئے انڈے	2عدد \n
چکن بون لیس 300گرام \n
کھانے کا تیل\n	2کھانے کے چمچ \n
پیاز	1کپ \n
بادام 1چوتھائی کپ \n
کاجو 1چوتھائی کپ \n
پستہ	1کھانے کا چمچ \n
ادرک لہسن پیسٹ 1چائے کا چمچ \n
ہلدی پاؤڈر	1چوتھائی چائے کا چمچ \n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ \n
لال مرچ پاؤڈر\n	1کھانے کا چمچ \n
گرم مصالحہ\n	آدھا چائے کا چمچ \n
\nدھنیا پاؤڈر	آدھا چائے کا چمچ \n
ہری مرچوں کی پیسٹ\n	1چائے کا چمچ \n
لیموں کا رس	آدھا کھانے کا چمچ \n
ٹماٹر پیسٹ	2کھانے کے چمچ \n
ذیرہ آدھا چائے کا چمچ \n
\nپیسٹ اجزاء:\n
ذیرہ 1کھانے کا چمچ\n
دھنیا 2کھانے کے چمچ\n
کالی الائچی	1عدد\n
سبز الائچی	4عدد\n
تیز پت	2عدد\n
جویں 05-07عدد\n
جاوتری 1عدد\n
دارچینی	1عدد\n
کالی مرچ 1کھانے کا چمچ\n
بادام 1کھانے کا چمچ\n
کاجو 1کھانے کا چمچ\n
کھانے کا تیل	1کپ\n
تلا ہوا پیاز آدھا کپ\n
گریوی اجزاء:\n
کھانے کا تیل\n	2کھانے کے چمچ\n
پانی	1کپ\n
ادرک لہسن پیسٹ	1کپ\n
ٹماٹر پیسٹ 1کھانے کا چمچ\n
میرینیٹڈ مصالحہ	بچا ہوا\n
ڈرائی فروٹس پیسٹ	1کپ\n
لال مرچ پاؤڈر	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ\n
دہی	آدھا کپ\n
کریم	آدھا کپ\n
مکھن	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
لیموں کا رس	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
ہری مرچیں گارنش کے لئے\n
ہرا دھنیا گارنش کے لئے\n

\nترکیب:\n
ہول چکن کو نمک اور سرکہ کے ساتھ دھو کر ہول چکن کو کٹ لگا لیں۔\n
اب ایک باؤل میں ادرک لہسن پیسٹ، دہی، الائچی پاؤڈر، ہری مرچوں کی پیسٹ، دھنیا پاؤڈر، لا ل مرچ پاؤڈر، نمک، ذیرہ اور سرکہ ڈال کر اچھی طرح مکس کرلیں۔\n
پھر ہول چکن کو اس مکسچر میں اچھی طرح میرینیٹ کر کے چار گھنٹے فریج میں رکھ دیں۔\n
اب ایک پین میں کھانے کا تیل گرم کر کے اس میں پیاز اور ڈرائی فروٹس ڈال کر ایک منٹ کے لئے بھون لیں۔\n
پھر اس میں ادرک لہسن پیسٹ، ہلدی پاؤڈر، لال مرچ پاؤڈر اور نمک ڈال کر اچھی طرح مکس کریں۔\n
اب اس میں ابلے ہوئے انڈے ڈال کر گولڈن ہونے تک پکائیں۔\n
پھر اس میں سے انڈے نکال کر اس میں چکن قیمہ اور پسے ہوئے ٹماٹر ڈال کر چکن کا رنگ بدلنے تک پکائیں۔\n
اب اس میں گرم مصالحہ، ذیرہ پاؤڈر، ہری مرچوں کی پیسٹ اور لیموں کا رس ڈال کر پانی خشک ہونے تک پکائیں۔\n
پھر میرینیٹڈ چکن لے کر اس میں تیار کیا ہوا چکن قیمہ اور انڈے ڈالیں۔\n
اب ہول چکن کی دونوں ٹانگوں کو اچھی طرح دھاگے سے باندھ لیں اور ٹوتھ پِک سے بند کر دیں۔\n
پھر ایک پین میں کھانے کا تیل گرم کر کے ہول چکن کو ہر سائیڈ سے پانچ منٹ کے لئے فرائی کر لیں۔\n
اب ایک پین میں ذیرہ، دھنیا، کالی الائچی، سبز الائچی، تیز پت، جویں، جاوتری، دار چینی اور کالی مرچ ڈال کر دو منٹ کے لئے روسٹ کر لیں۔\n
پھر ایک گرینڈر میں روسٹ کئے ہوئے مصالحے، تلا ہوا پیاز اور ڈرائی فروٹس ڈال کر گرینڈ کر کے گاڑھا پیسٹ بنا لیں۔ اب ایک دوسرے پین میں کھانے کا تیل گرم کرکے اس میں ادرک لہسن پیسٹ، بچا ہوا مصالحہ، پسے ہوئے ٹماٹر، ڈرائی فروٹس پیسٹ، لا ل مرچ پاؤڈر، نمک پانی اوردہی ڈال کر گریوی بنا لیں۔\n
پھر اس میں کریم، پکا ہوا ہول چکن، ہری مرچیں، مکھن، لیموں کا رس اور چوپڈ دھنیا ڈال کر درمیانی آنچ پر آئل علیحدہ ہونے تک پکائیں۔\n
اب ہول چکن کو ایک سرونگ ڈِش میں رکھیں اور اس پر گریوی ڈال کر گرم گرم سرو کریں۔\n
تیاری کا وقت : 20 منٹ\n
</string>
    <string name="kofta">\nکوفتہK and Ns Stok 400g
\nچاول\n
کھڑا مصالحہ\n
تیز پات	1\n
لونگ	4\n
ثابت کالی مرچ	6-8\n
چھوٹی دار چینی	2\n
ادرک لہسن پیسٹ	1چائے کا چمچ\n
تلا ہوا پیاز	آدھا کپ\n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ\n
لال مرچ پاؤڈر	1چائے کا چمچ\n
دہی	آدھا کپ\n
ہری مرچ باریک کٹی 	2-3\n
گرم مصالحہ پاؤڈر	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
سونف	آدھا کپ\n
کھانے کا تیل	2-3کھانے کے چمچ\n

\nترکیب:\n
ایک پین میں تیل گرم کریں اس میں کھڑا مصالحہ، ادرک لہسن پیسٹ، تلا ہوا پیازڈال کر اچھی طرح مکس کر لیں ۔\n
نمک، لال مرچ، گرم مصالحہ ، سونف ڈال کر اچھی طرح 1-2منٹ پکا لیں ۔\n
دہی ڈال کر مکس کریں اور ہلکی آنچ پر 4-5منٹ پکائیں۔\n
پانی ڈال کر بھگوئے ہوئے چاول، K and Ns Stok ڈال کر اچھی طرح مکس کر لیں ۔\n
کو پیکٹ پر دی گئی ہدایات کے مطابق نرم کر لیں \n
کوفتوں کو چاولوں میں ڈال کر 15منٹ ہلکی آنچ پر دم دیں۔\n
کوفتہ پلاؤ تیار ہے۔\n
باریک کٹی ہوئی لال مرچ اور رائتہ کے ساتھ سرو کریں۔\n
تیاری کا وقت : 10 Minutes\n
پکانے کا وقت : 25-30 Minutes</string>
    <string name="Malai"> \nچکن بون لیس کیوب کٹنگ 400گرام
\n۔ نمک حسبِ ذائقہ\n
۔ ادرک لہسن پیسٹ ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
۔ لیموں کا رس ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
۔ ہری مرچ دو عدد\n
۔ سفید مرچ پاؤڈر ایک چائے کا چمچ\n
۔ دھنیا پاؤڈر ایک چائے کا چمچ\n
۔ زیرہ پاؤڈر ایک چائے کا چمچ\n
۔ بادام ،کاجواور پستہ پاؤڈر دو کھانے کے چمچ\n
۔ کریم تین کھانے کے چمچ\n
۔ کھانے کاتیل ڈیڑھ کھانے کا چمچ\n

\nترکیب\n
۔ ایک برتن میں چکن لیں اور اس میں نمک،ادرک لہسن پیسٹ ،لیموں کا رس ،ہری مرچ ،سفید مرچ پاؤڈر ،دھنیا پاؤڈر ،زیرہ پاؤڈر ،بادام کاجو اور پستہ پاؤڈر ،کریم اور کھانے کا تیل ڈال کراچھی طرح ملا ئیں اور ایک گھنٹے کے لیے فریج میں رکھ دیں ۔\n
۔ اب کوئلے پر باربی کیو کر لیں یا 230ڈگری سینٹی گریڈ پر تیس منٹ تک اوون بیک کر لیں ۔\n
آپکی مزیدار ملائی بوٹی تیار ہے ۔\n
\nپکا نے کا وقت : ایک گھنٹہ </string>
    <string name="cholay">
چکن لیگز چار سو گرام\n
کھانے کا تیل آدھا کپ\n
پیاز چوپ ایک عدد\n
ثابت زیرہ ایک چائے کا چمچ\n
سبز مرچ چوپ دو عدد\n
ادرک لہسن پیسٹ ڈیڑہ کھانے کا چمچ\n
ٹماٹر دو عدد\n
دہی دو کھانے کے چمچ\n
نمک حسبِ ذائقہ\n
گرم پانی ایک کپ\n
اُبلے ہوئے سفید چنے ڈیڑھ کپ\n
لاہوری مرغ چھولے مصالحہ دو کھانے کے چمچ\n

لاہوری مرغ مصالحہ بنانے کا طریقہ:\n
اجزاء\n
نمک ایک کھانے کاچمچ\n
ثابت دھنیا دو کھانے کے چمچ\n
ثابت زیرہ دو کھانے کے چمچ\n
لونگ آٹھ عدد\n
لال مرچ کُٹی ہوئی دو کھانے کے چمچ\n
دار چینی تین عدد\n
بڑی اِلائچی تین عدد\n
بادیان دو عدد\n
سبز اِلائچی چار عدد\n
چکن پاؤڈر تین کھانے کے چمچ\n
میتھا سوڈا آدھا چائے کاچمچ\n
\nاجوائن ایک چوتھائی چائے کا چمچ
جلوتری پانچ گرام\n
ہلدی ایک چائے کا چمچ\n
ان سب کو بھون کر گرائینڈ کر لیں اور استعمال کر یں ۔\n
ترکیب\n
۔ایک پین میں ثابت لاہوری مُرغ مصالحہ لیں اور بھون کر گرائینڈ کر لیں۔\n
۔اب ایک پین میں کھانے کا تیل لیں اور ا س میں پیاز ،ثابت زیرہ اورسبز مر چ ڈال کر لائٹ براؤن کر لیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں ادرک لہسن پیسٹ، چکن لیگز ،ٹماٹر ،دہی ،نمک اور لاہوری مرغ چھولے مصالحہ ڈال کر دوسے تین منٹ بھونائی کر لیں ۔\n
اب اس میں گرم پانی (آدھا کپ )ڈال کر آٹھ سے دس منٹ تک دم دیں اور دو سے تین منٹ تک بھونائی کرلیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں اُبلے ہوئے سفید چنے اور گرم پانی (آدھا کپ ) ڈال کر ایک سے دو منٹ تک پکا لیں ۔\n
۔اب اسے دو سے تین منٹ تک دم دینے کے بعدگارنش کر لیں ۔\n
آپکا مزیدار لاہوری مرغ چھولے مصالحہ تیار ہے ۔\n
\nپکانے کا وقت: ایک گھنٹہ</string>
    <string name="shawaarma">ڈو بنانے کے اجزا:\n
میدہ	ڈھائی کپ\n
کھانے کا تیل	2 کھانے کے چمچ\n
چینی	1 چائے کا چمچ\n
ایسٹ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
نمک	1 چائے کا چمچ\n
نیم گرم پانی	حسبِ ضرورت\n

چکن میرینیشن کے اجزاء:\n
چکن(بونلیس)	400 گرام\n
لال مرچ پاؤڈر	1 چائے کا چمچ\n
کالی مرچ آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
زیرہ پاؤڈر	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
گر م مصالحہ	1چائے کا چمچ\n
ادرک لہسن پیسٹ	1چائے کا چمچ\n
لیموں کا رس	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
دہی	2 کھانے کا چمچ\n
بار بی کیو سوس	1کھانے کا چمچ\n

سلاد بنانے کے اجزا:\n
سلاد پتہ چوپ	آدھا کپ\n
گاجر جولین	آدھا کپ\n
کھیرا  جولین	آدھا کپ\n
ہرا دھنیا	چوتھائی کپ\n
نمک	حسبِ ضرورت\n
سرکہ	دو کھانے کے چمچ\n
پانی	ایک چوتھائی کپ\n

ڈو بنانے کی ترکیب:\n
ایک برتن میں میدہ لیں اس میں کھانے کا تیل ، چینی، نمک، ایسٹ ڈال کر ملا لیں اب اس میں نیم گرم پانی ڈال کر گوندھ لیں۔\n
اب اس کو ڈھک کر ایک سے دو گھنٹہ رکھ دیں۔\n
اب اس کے بیڑے بنا لیں اور بیل لیں اب اس کو توہ پہ پکا لیں۔\n
چکن تیار کرنے کی ترکیب:\n
ایک برتن میں چکن لیں اس میں ادرک لہسن پیسٹ ، دہی، بار بی کیو سوس، نمک، زیرہ، کالی مرچ، لال مرچ، لیموں کا رس ڈال کر دو گھنٹے میرینیٹ کر لیں،\n
اب اس کو پین میں دو کھانے کے چمچ تیل ڈال کر فرائی کر لیں۔\n
سلاد بنانے کا طریقہ:\n
ایک برتن میں سلاد پتہ، کھیرا، گاجر، ہرا دھنیا، سرکہ، نمک،پانی ڈال کر ملا لیں۔\n
سوس بنانے کا طریقہ:v
ایک برتن میں مایونیز، دہین، کالی مرچ، سفید مرچ، لہسن ڈال کر ملا لیں۔\n
اسمبلنگ:\n
طریقہ ایک:\n
سوارما بریڈ پر تیار کی ہوئی سوس، کیچپ، سلاد، چکن، جالا پینو ڈال کر رول کر لیں اور اس کو لکڑی کی سٹک سے پرو لیں۔\n
طریقہ دو:\n
سوارما بریڈ پر تیار کی ہوئی سوس، کیچپ، سلادپتہ، چکن، جالا پینو ڈال کر بٹر پیپر سے رول کر لیں۔\n
پکانے کا وقت : 30 Minutes\n
</string>
    <string name="salad">اُ بلے ہوئے آلو چارسو گرام\n
اُبلی ہوئی گاجر تین سو گرام\n
سیب ایک کلو\n
اُبلے ہوئے مٹر دو سو گرام\n
مایو نیز چار سو گرام\n
کریم ایک کپ\n
آئسنگ شوگر تین سو گرام\n
نمک حسبِ ذئاقہ\n
سفید مر چ ایک چوتھائی چائے کا چمچ\n
مکس فروٹ دو سو گرام\n
کالا انگور دو سو گرام\n
پستہ پانچ گرام\n
بادام پانچ گرام\n
ترکیب\n
۔ایک باؤل میں اُبلے ہوئے آلو لیں اور اس میں اُبلی ہوئی گاجر،سیب ،اُبلے ہوئے مٹر ،مایو نیز ،کریم ،آئسنگ شوگر، نمک اور سفید مرچ ڈال کر مکس کرلیں ۔\n
۔اب اس پر مکس فروٹ ،کالے انگور ،پستہ اور بادام کی گارنش کر لیں ۔\n
۔آپکی مزیدار رشین سلاد تیار ہے ۔\n
بنانے کا وقت: بیس منٹ\n</string>
    <string name="karaylay">کریلے 5عدد\n
پانی	1 کپ\n
کھانے کا تیل	6کھانے کے چمچ\n
ادرک لہسن پیسٹ	1چائے کا چمچ\n
پیاز سلائس	1کپ\n
ٹماٹر	1کپ\n
کُٹا دھنیا	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
کُٹی لال مرچ	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
زیرہ پاؤڈر	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
لال مرچ پاؤڈر	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
پانی	1کپ\n
ہرا دھنیا	2 کھانے کے چمچ\n
ہری مرچ	2-3 عدد\n

فلنگ بنانے کے اجزاء:\n
بیف قیمہ	1کلو\n
پیاز چوپ	ڈیڑھ کپ\n
ادرک لہسن پیسٹ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
زیرہ	1چائے کا چمچ\n
لال مرچ پاؤڈر	1 چائے کا چمچ\n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ\n
زیرہ پاؤڈر	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
لال مرچ کُٹی ہوئی	1 چائے کا چمچ\n
گرم مصالحہ	1 کھانے کا چمچ\n
ہلدی	1چائے کا چمچ\n
ٹماٹر	1 کپ\n
دھنیا پاؤڈر	1چائے کا چمچ\n
دہی	آدھا کپ\n
کھانے کا تیل	4 کھانے کا چمچ\n
ہری مرچ	2-3 عدد\n

فلنگ بنانے کی ترکیب :\n
ایک پین میں قیمہ، پانی ڈال کر چھ سے آٹھ منٹ پکا لیں۔\n
\nاب اس میں پیاز، ادرک لہسن پیسٹ، زیرہ ، لال مرچ پاؤڈڑ، نمک، زیرہ، کُٹی لال مرچ، گرم مصالحہ،ہلدی،دھنیا پاؤڈرڈال کر تھوڑی دیر پکا لیں۔
اب اس میں ٹماٹر، دہی، ہری مرچ، کھانے کا تیل ڈال کر گلنے تک بھون لیں۔\n
کریلے بنانے کی ترکیب:\n
کریلوں کو پہلے چھیل لیں اور اس میں سے بیج نکال لیں اب اس پر نمک لگا دیں اور ایک سے دو گھنٹے کے لیے رکھ دیں۔\n
اب ان کو دوھ لیں ۔ اب ململ کے کپڑے میں ان کریلوں کو رکھ کر نچوڑ لیں۔\n
اب ان کریلوں میں تیار کیا ہوا قیمہ بھر لیں اور دھگہ سے کریلوں کو بند کر لیں۔\n
اب ان کو گرم تیل لیں شیلو فرائی کر لیں۔\n
کریلے اور قیمہ بنانے کا طریقہ:\n
ایک پین میں کھانے ک تیل چھ کھانے کا چمچ لیں اس میں ادرک لہسن پیسٹ، پیاز ڈال کر پیاز نرم ہونے تک پکا لیں،۔\n
اب اس میں ٹماٹر ڈال کر تھوڑی دیر پکا لیں۔\n
اب اس میں دھنیا، زیرہ، لال مرچ ڈال کر تھوڑی دیر پکا لیں۔\n
اب اس میں باقی بچا ہوا تیار قیمہ ڈال دیں اور ییار کیے ہوے کریلے اور پانی ڈال کر پانچ سے چھ منٹ ڈھک کر پکا لیں۔\n
ہرا دھنیا، ہری مرچ بطور گارنش استعما ل کر لیں۔\n
پکانے کا وقت : 40 Minutes\n</string>
    <string name="WhiteChick">چکن	500گرام\n
کھانے کا تیل	4کھانے کے چمچ\n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ\n
ادرک لہسن پیسٹ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
گرم مصالحہ	1چائے کا چمچ\n
کالی مرچ 1 چائے کا چمچ\n
ہری مرچ چوپ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
دھنیا پاؤڈر	1چائے کا چمچ\n
دہی	1 کپ\n
کریم	آدھا کپ\n
زیرہ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n

ترکیب:\n
ایک کڑاہی میں کھانے کا تیل لیں اب اس میں چکن ڈال کر تھوڑی دیر پکا لیں ۔\n
اب اس میں ادرک لہسن پیسٹ ڈال کر تھوڑی دیر پکا لیں۔\n
اب اس میں گرم مصالحہ، کالی مرچ، دھنیا پاؤڈر ڈال کر تھوڑی دیر پکا لیں۔\n
اب اس میں دہی ڈال کر چار سے پانچ منٹ پکا لیں۔\n
اب اس میں کریم ڈال کر ایک سے دو منٹ تک پکا لیں۔\n
\nپکانے کا وقت : 30 Minutes</string>
    <string name="Pakora">اچاری مصالحہ کے اجزاء:\n
ثابت دھنیا	ڈیڑھ کھانے کا چمچ\n
رائی	1چائے کا چمچ\n
میتھی دانہ	آدا چائے کا چمچ\n
سونف	1چائے کا چمچ\n

چکن میرینیشن کے اجزاء:\n
چکن(بونلیس)	آدھا کلو\n
دہی	آدھا کپ\n
اچاری مصالحہ	1چائے کا چمچ\n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ\n
ادرک لہسن پیسٹ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
کُٹی لامرچ	1چائے کا چمچ\n
لیموں کا رس 2 کھانے کے چمچ\n
ہلدی آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
گرم مصالحہ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n

بیسن مکسچر بنانے کے اجزاء:\n
بیسن	1کپ\n
کُٹی لال مرچ	1چائے کا چمچ\n
کلونجی	1چائے کا چمچ\n
کارن فلور	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ\n
پانی حسبِ ضرورت\n

اچاری مصالحہ بنانے کی ترکیب:\n
ایک گرائینڈرمیں ثابت دھنیا، رائی، میتھی دانہ، سونف ڈال کر اچھی طرح گرائینڈ کر لیں۔\n
چکن میرینیٹ:\n
ایک برتن میں چکن لیں، دہی اچاری مصالحہ، نمک،ادرک لہسن پیسٹ،کُٹی لامرچ،لیموں کا رس ،ہلدی،گرم مصالحہ ڈال کر اچھی طرح ملا لیں ۔\n
اب اس کو بیس منٹ کے لیے فریج میں رکھ دیں۔\n
بیسن مکسچر بنانے کی ترکیب:\n
ایک برتن میں بیسن لیں اس میں کلونجی،کارن فلور،نمک،پانی ڈال ملا لیں اور تھوڑا گاڑھا رہنے دیں تاکہ چکن پر لگ سکے۔\n
اب چکن کو اس میں ملا لیں اور درمیانی آنچ پر فرائی کر لیں۔\n
آپکے مزے دار چکن اچاری پکوڑا تیار ہے۔\n
    تیاری کا وقت:	30\n منٹ</string>
    <string name="muttonB">چاول بنانے کے اجزاء\n
گارڈ سپریم باسمتی	700 گرام\n
پانی	حسبِ ضرورت\n

پیاز کا پیسٹ بنانے کے اجزاء:\n
بادام	12-15\n
فرائی کی ہوئی پیاز	1کپ\n
پانی	حسبِ ضرورت\n

مٹن میرینٹ کے اجزاء:\n
مٹن	1کلو\n
ادرک لہسن	2 کھانے کا چمچ\n
دھنیا پاؤڈر	2کھانے کا چمچ\n
نمک	حسبِ ضرورت\n
لال مرچ پاؤڈر	ڈیڑھ کھانے کا چمچ\n
گرم مصالحہ	1 چائے کا چمچ\n
ہلدی پاؤڈر	1 چائے کا چمچ\n
دہی	1 کپ\n

چاول اُبالنے کے اجزاء:\n
کھانے کا تیل	1کھانے کا تیل\n
سرکہ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
گرم مصالحہ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
زیرہ	آدھا کھانے کا چمچ\n
چاول(بھیگے ہوئے)	700گرام\n

مٹن مصالحے کے اجزاء:\n
کھانے کا تیل	1 کھانے کا چمچ\n
پیاز کا پیسٹ\n
مٹن  مصالحہ لگا \n
گرم مصالحہ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
زیرہ	آدھا کھانے کا چمچ\n
ٹماٹر چوپ	1 عدد\n
پانی	آدھا کپ\n

اسمبلنگ کے اجزاء:\n
مٹن مصالحہ\n
چاول\n
فرائی کی ہوئی پیاز	1کپ\n
ہرادھنیا	1کپ\n
پودنیہ	1کپ\n
کیوڑا 1چائے کا چمچ\n
پیلا رنگ	1 چائے کاچمچ\n
        زعفران دودھ میں ملا	1 چائے کا چمچ\n

ترکیب\n
ایک برتن میں چاول اور پانی ڈال کر بائیس سے پچیس منٹ تک بھیگو دیں۔\n
ایک برتن میں پانی لیں اس میں چاول، کھانے کا تیل، سرکہ، ثابت گرم مصالحہ، زیرہ، چاول ڈال کر تین چوتھائی گلنے تک پکا لیں۔\n
پیازپیسٹ بنانے کی ترکیب:\n
ایک گرائینڈربادام، فرائی کی ہوئی پیاز، پانی ڈال کرگرائینڈ کر لیں (ملائم پیسٹ بنا لیں)\n
مٹن میرینیشن:\n
ایک برتن میں مٹن لیں اس میں ادرک لہسن پیسٹ، دھنیا پاؤڈڑ، نمک، لال مرچ، گرم مصالحہ، ہلدی، دہی ڈال کر اچھی طرح ملا لیں ۔\n
چارسے پانچ گھنٹے فریج میں رکھ دیں۔\n
مٹن مصالحہ بنانے کا ترکیب:\n
ایک برتن میں کھانے کاتیل لیں اس میں میرینٹ کیا ہوا مٹن ڈال کر آٹھ سے دس منٹ تک پکا لیں۔\n
اب اس نے گرم مصالحہ، زیرہ، پیازکا پیسٹ، ٹماٹرچوپ اور پانی ڈال کر بیس سے پچیس منٹ تک (اچھی طرح گلنے تک)۔\n
بریانی کی تہہ لگانے کا طریقہ:\n\n
ایک برتن میں تیار کیا ہوا مصا لحہ ڈال کر پھیلا لیں، اب اس پر چاول ڈال کر پھیلا لیں۔\n
اب اس پر ہرا دھنیا، ہری مرچ پھیلا دیں۔\n
ا ب اس پر تیار کیا ہوا مٹن مصالحہ اور اوبلے ہوئے چاول کی تہہ بچھا لیں۔\n
اب اس ہر فرائی کی ہوئی پیاز، دھنیا ، پودینہ، کیوڑا واٹر، پیلا رنگ ڈال کر ڈھک دیں اور آتھ سے دس منٹ تک دم دیں۔\n
تیاری کا وقت : 30 minutes\n
پکانے کا وقت : 30 minutes\n</string>
    \n
    <string name="rosh">
کھانے کا تیل	4-5 کھانے کے چمچ\n
لہسن چوپ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
مٹن	1 کلو\n
ہلدی	ایک چو تھائی چائے کا چمچ\n
زیرہ	1چائے کا چمچ\n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ\n
کالی مرچ کُٹی ہوئی	1چائے کا چمچ\n
پانی	حسبِ ضرورت\n
ٹماٹر درمیان سے کٹی ہوئی 	3 عدد\n
پیاز درمیان سے کٹی ہوئی	3عدد\n
ہری مرچ	3-4\n

ترکیب\n
ایک برتن میں کھانے کا تیل، لہسن چوپ ڈال کر تھوڑی دیر پکا لیں\n
اب اس میں مٹن، ہلدی، زیرہ، نمک، کالی مرچ کُٹی ہوئی، پانی ڈال کرفوئل پیپر سے کور کر کے ڈھک دیں اور دو سے تین گھنٹے ہلکی آنچ پر پکا لیں۔\n
اب اس میں پیاز، ٹماٹر، ہری مرچ ڈال کر دھک دیں اور بارہ سے پندرہ منٹ تک ہلکی درمیانی آنچ پر پکا لیں۔\n
پکانے کا وقت : 3-4 Hours\n</string>
    <string name="Qorma">پیاز پیسٹ:\n
فرائی پیاز ایک اور آدھا کپ\n
دہی	آدھا کپ\n
سبز الائچی	3\n
پانی	آدھا کپ\n
اجزاء:\n
بیف 1 کلو\n
کھانے کا تیل	3چوتھائی\n
ادرک لہسن پیسٹ	2کھانے کے چمچ\n
ثابت مصالحہ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
دہی 1کپ\n
پانی حسبِ ضرورت\n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ\n
لال مرچ پاؤڈر	2چائے کے چمچ\n
دھنیے کا پاؤڈر	1چائے کا چمچ\n
ادرک سجاوٹ کیلئے	2کھانے کے چمچ\n
دھنیا سجاوٹ کیلئے	1کھانے کا چمچ\n

ترکیب:\n
ایک بلینڈر میں دہی، سبز الائچی ، فرائی پیازاور پانی ڈالیں اور اچھی طرح مکس کر لیں\n
اب ایک برتن میں کھانے کا تیل گرم کریں ، ادرک لہسن پیسٹ ڈ ال کر مکس کر لیں\n
اب ثابت مصالحہ اور بیف ڈال کر اچھی طرح مکس کر لیں،اور 2سے3منٹ کے لئے پکائیں\n
پانی ڈالیں ، اور ڈھکن سے ڈھک کر بیف تقریباََ گلنے تک پکائیں(اگر ضرورت ہوتو پانی اور ڈالا جا سکتا ہے)\n
دہی ، نمک ، لال مرچ پاؤڈراور دھنیا ڈال کے مکس کریں اور 2سے3منٹ تک بھون لیں\n
پیاز کا پیسٹ ڈالیں اور 3سے4منٹ پکائیں\n
ڈھکن ڈھک کر درمیانی آنچ پر پانچ منٹ کے لئے پکائیں\n
باریک کٹا ہوا ادرک اور دھنیا اوپر چھڑک کر گرم گرم نان کے ساتھ سرو کر دیں\n
\nپکانے کا وقت : 40 Minutes</string>
    <string name="alonan">ڈو بنانے کے اجزاء:\n
میدہ	3 کپ\n
نمک	1 چائے کاچمچ\n
دہی	2کھانے کے چمچ\n
کھانے کا تیل	ڈھائی کھانے کے چمچ\n
چینی	2 کھانے کے چمچ\n
ایسٹ	2 چائے کا چمچ\n
پانی	حسبِ ضرورت\n

آلو کی فلنگ بنانے کے اجزاء:\n
آلو اُبال کر پیس لیں	2 کپ\n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ\n
گرم مصا لحہ	1 چائے کاچمچ\n
انار دانہ	1 چائے کاچمچ\n
ہرادھنیا	1-2 کھانے کے چمچ\n
لیموں کا رس	آدھا لیموں\n
پیاز چوپ	ایک چوتھائی کپ\n
ہری مرچ چوپ	2 عدد\n
چاٹ مصالحہ	1 چائے کاچمچ\n
لال مرچ پاؤڈر	1 چائے کاچمچ\n
ثابت دھنیا	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n

آلو کباب سٹفڈ نان بنانے کے اجزاء\n
ڈو	حسبِ ضرورت\n
آلو کی فلنگ	حسبِ ضرورت\n
	400گرام K and Ns Kafta Kabab\n
دودھ	2کھانے کے چمچ\n

ڈو بنانے کی ترکیب\n
ایک برتن میں میدہ لیں اس میں نمک، دہی، دو کھانے کے چمچ کھانے کا تیل، چینی، ایسٹ اور پانی ڈال کر اچھی طرح گوندھ لیں۔\n
اب اس پر ایک چائے کا چمچ کھانے کا تیل ڈو پر لگا دیں اور تیس سے پینتیس منٹ کے لیے ڈھک کر رکھ دیں۔ \n
اب ڈو کو دوبارہ تین سے چارمنٹ تک گوندھ لیں۔ \n
آلو فلنگ بنانے کی ترکیب\n
ایک برتن میں آلو، نمک، گرم مصالحہ، انار دانہ، ہرا دھنیا، لیموں کا رس، پیاز، ہری مرچ، چاٹ مصالحہ، لال مرچ، ثابت دھنیا ڈال کر اچھی طرح ملا لیں۔\n
کباب کو پیکٹ پر دی گئی ہدایات کے مطا بق تیار کر لیں۔\n
ڈو کا ایک بڑا پیڑا بنا لیں اور ایک چھوٹا پیڑا بنا لیں۔\n
اب بڑے پیڑے کو بیل لیں اور اس ک درمیان میں تیار کیا ہوا آلو کا مصالحہ رکھ دیں۔\n
اب چھوٹا پیڑا بیل لیں۔اور اس پر پانی لگا کر تیار کیے ہوئے مصالحہ پر رکھ کر ڈو کو دبا کر ملا لیں۔\n
اب اس پر کانٹے سے چھوٹی ڈو پر نشان لگا لیں۔\n
تیار کیے ہوئے کباب کو ڈو پر دائرے میں رکھ دیں اور اس کو ڈو سے لپیٹ لیں ۔\n
اب اس پر برش کی مدد سے ددھ لگا لیں اور اس کو اچھی طرح لپیٹ کر منہ بند کر لیں۔\n
اب کر بڑے (موٹی تہہ والا) برتن کو چار سے پانچ منٹ گرم کر لیں اور اب اس تیار کیے ہوئے نان کو بیکنگ والی ٹرے میں رکھ کر اس گرم برتن میں رکھ دیں اور اس کو ڈھک کر بارہ سے پندرہ منٹ تک پکا لیں۔\n
یا پھر اس نان کو دس سے بارہ منٹ تک 180 ڈگری سینٹی گریڈ پر اون بیک کر لیں۔\n
تیاری کا وقت : 50 Minutes\n</string>
    <string name="macroni">مکرونی چاٹ\n
چاٹ مصالحہ کے اجزاء\n
زیرہ پاؤڈر	2 کھانے کے چمچ\n
ثابت لال مرچ	15عدد\n
سونف	1 کھانے کا چمچ\n
ثا بت دھنیا	4 کھانے کے چمچ\n
ٹاٹری	1 کھانے کا چمچ\n
کالی مرچ پاؤڈر	1 کھانے کاچمچ\n
اجوائن	1 چائے کا چمچ\n
کالا نمک	1 کھانے کا چمچ\n
ادرک پاؤڈر	1 چائے کا چمچ\n
آم چور	1 کھانے کا چمچ\n

مکرونی چاٹ کے اجزاء\n
کھانے کا تیل حسبِ ضرورت\n
مکرونی اُبلی ہوئی	ڈیڑھ کپ\n
آلو اُبلے ہوئے	1 کپ\n
شملہ مرچ کیوب کٹ	تین چوتھائی کپ\n
پیاز چوپ	1 درمیانی\n
ٹماٹر چوپ	2 چھوٹے\n
ہرا دھنیا	آدھا کپ\n
نمک	حسب ذائقہ\n
چاٹ مصالحہ	2 کھانے کا چمچ\n
ہری مرچ چوپ	2-3عدد\n
املی چٹنی	3 کھانے کا چمچ\n
لیموں کا رس	2کھانے کا چمچ\n

چاٹ مصالحہ بنانے کی ترکیب:\n
ایک پین میں زیرہ ڈال کر ہلکا سا بھون لیں۔\n
اب اس میں ثابت لال مرچ، دھنیا، سونف ڈال کر فرائی کر لیں۔\n
اب ان کو گرائینڈر میں ڈال کر گرائینڈ کر لیں۔\n
اب اس گرائینڈ کیے ہوئے مصالحہ کو ایک برتن میں ڈال دیں اب اس میں ٹاٹری، کالی مرچ ؤڈر، اجوائن، ادرک پاؤڈر، آم چور ڈال کر اچھی طرح ملا لیں۔\n
اس مصالحہ لو ڈبہ میں ڈال لیں اور چار سے چھ ہفتہ تک استعمال کر سکتے ہیں۔\n
مکرونی سلاد بنانے کی ترکیب
ایک برتن میں پانی لیں اس میں تھوڑا سا کھانے کا تیل ڈال کر مکرونی ڈال دیں اور اُبال لیں۔ \n
اُبلی ہوئی مکرونی کو برتن میں ڈال لیں اور اس میں اُبلے ہوئے آلو، شملہ مرچ، پیاز، ٹماٹر، ہرا دھنیا، چاٹ امصالحہ، ہری مرچ، املی چٹنی، لیموں کا رس ڈال کر اچھی طرح ملا لیں۔\n
</string>
    <string name="tikkapulao">
 515گرامK and Ns Mughlai Tikka \n
چاول	500 گرام\n
ادرک لہسن پیسٹ	1 کھانے کا چمچ\n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ\n
پیاز	1 عدد\n
دہی	آدھا کپ\n
لال مرچ کُٹی ہوئی	1چائے کا چمچ\n
دھنیا کُٹا ہوا	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
زیرہ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
ثابت گرم مصالحہ	5گرام\n
پیلا رنگ	تین چوتھائی چائے کا چمچ\n
مکھن	3 کھانے کے چمچ\n
گھی	3 کھانے کے چمچ\n
ہری مرچ	2 150 3عدد\n
دودھ	1کپ\n
بادام(بھیگے ہوئے)	25 گرام\n
پستہ	25 گرام\n
کشمش	25 گرام\n

مغلائی تکہ پلاؤ بنانے کی ترکیب\n
مغلائی تکہ پیکٹ پر دی گئی ہدایات کے مطابق تیار کر لیں۔\n
ایک پین میں گھی اور تیل ڈال کر گرم کر لیں اب اس میں پیاز، ادرک لہسن پیسٹ ڈال کر ایک سے دو منٹ فرائی کر لیں۔\n
اب اس میں گرم مصالحہ ڈال کرگولڈن ہونے تک فرائی کر لیں۔\n
اب اس میں ہری مرچ، دہی، لال مرچ کُٹی ہوئی، کُٹا دھنیا،زیرہ، ڈال کر ایک سے دو منٹ پکا لیں۔\n
اب اس میں بھیگے ہوئے چاول ڈال دیں اور پانی ڈال دیں۔\n
تھوڑی دیر پکانے کے بعد اس میں دودھ ، پستہ، بادام ڈال کر ملا لیں۔\n
اب اس کو ڈھک دیں اور آٹھ سے دس منٹ تک دم دیں۔\n
</string>
    <string name="shashlik">
چکن میرینیٹ کے اجزاء\n
چکن بونلیس	500گرام\n
ادرک لہسن پیسٹ	1 کھانے کا چمچ\n
ہلدی	1چائے کا چمچ\n
سویا سوس	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
لال مرچ پاؤڈر	1چائے کا چمچ\n
کالی مرچ	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ\n
گرم مصالحہ	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
دھنیا پاؤڈر	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
سرکہ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
زیرہ پاؤڈر	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
کریم	2 کھانے کے چمچ\n

سوس بنانے کے اجزاء\n
رفحان کارن آئل	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
لہسن چوپ	1چائے کا چمچ\n
ادرک چوپ	1چائے کا چمچ\n
کیچپ	آدھا کپ\n
کالی مرچ	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
سرکہ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
چلی سوس	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
سفید مرچ	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
لال مرچ کُٹی ہوئی	1چائے کا چمچ\n
اوریگانو	1چائے کا چمچ\n
پانی	ایک چوتھائی کپ\n

شاشلک سبزیاں:\n
شملہ مرچ لال ، پیلی، ہری	1عدد بڑی\n
ٹماٹر	1عددبڑا\n
پیاز	1عددبڑی\n

چکن میرینیٹ: ایک برتن میں چکن،ادرک لہسن پیسٹ،ہلدی،سویا سوس،لال مرچ پاؤڈر،کالی مرچ،نمک،گرم مصالحہ،دھنیا پاؤڈر،سرکہ،زیرہ پاؤڈر،کریم ڈال کر اچھی طرح ملا لیں اور پانچ سے چھ گھنٹے کے لیے فریج میں رکھ دیں۔ سوس بنانے کی ترکیب: ایک پین میں رفحان کورن آئل،لہسن(چوپ)،ادرک چوپ،کیچپ،کالی مرچ،سرکہ،چلی سوس،سفید مرچ،لال مرچ کُٹی ہوئی،اوریگانو ڈال کر تھوڑی دیر پکا لیں اب اس میں پانی ڈال کر دو سے تین منٹ پکا لیں۔ اسمبلنگ: شملہ مرچ، پیاز، ٹماٹر کو بڑے کیوب میں کاٹ لیں۔ اب تیار کیے ہوئے چکن کو سیکھ میں ایک بوٹی پھر شمہ مرچ کیوب، پیاز کیوب،ٹماٹر کیوب پھر بوٹی لگا کر سیکھ کو بھر لیں۔ اب ایک پین میں رفحان کورن آئل ایک کھانے کا چمچ ڈال کر ان سیکھیوں کو اس میں شیلو فرائی کر لیں۔ آپکی مزے دار چکن شاشلک تیار ہے۔\n
تیاری کا وقت : 20 Minutes\n
\nپکانے کا وقت : 20 Minutes</string>
    <string name="qeemabir">
بیف قیمہ 500 گرام\n
گارڈ الٹیمیٹ رائس 500گرام\n
پیاز 2 عدد\n
ٹماٹر 2عدد\n
دہی 00 2گرام\n
سبز مر چ 3عدد\n
کھانے کا تیل 2کھانے کے چمچ\n
نمک حسبِ ذائقہ\n
لال مرچ پاؤڈر 1چائے کا چمچ\n
لال مرچ کُٹی ہوئی 1 چائے کا چمچ\n
کا لی مرچ پاؤڈر 1/2چائے کاچمچ\n
دھنیا پاؤڈر 1-1/2چائے کاچمچ\n
زیرہ پاؤڈر 1-1/2چائے کا چمچ\n
گرم مصالحہ پاؤڈر 1 چائے کاچمچ\n
ثابت گرم مصالحہ پانچ گرام\n
ہلدی 1 چائے کاچمچ\n
سبز دھنیا 5گرام\n
پودینہ 5گرام\n
لیموں 2عدد\n
لہسن ادرک کُٹی ہوئی 2 کھانے کا چمچ\n
لہسن کُٹا ہوا 1 چائے کاچمچ\n
سرکہ ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
ایک چائے کاچمچ پیلا رنگ\n
ترکیب\n
۔ایک باؤ ل میں پانی لیں اوراس میں گارڈ الٹیمیٹ رائس ڈال کر پندرہ منٹ تک بھگو لیں ۔\n
۔اب ایک پین میں پانی لیں اوراس میں ثابت گرم مصالحہ ،کھانے کا تیل(1کھانے کا چمچ) ،سرکہ، نمک ڈال کر ایک کنی چھوڑ کر اُبال لیں ۔\n
۔اب ایک پین میں کھانے کا تیل(1کھانے کا چمچ) لیں اوراس میں پیاز ،لہسن کُٹا ہوا ورادرک کُٹی ہوئی ڈال کر براؤن کر لیں اوراس میں ٹماٹر ڈال کر پانچ منٹ تک پکالیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں نمک،لال مرچ پاؤڈر ،لال مرچ کُٹی ہوئی ،دھنیا پاؤڈر ،زیرہ پاؤڈر ،ہلدی پاؤڈر اور ثابت گرم مصالحہ ڈال کر دو منٹ تک پکالیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں بیف قیمہ ڈال کر تین منٹ تک بھون لیں اور دہی ڈال کر دو منٹ تک پکا لیں ۔\n
۔اب ا س میں پانی ڈال کر دس منٹ تک پکالیں ۔\n
۔اب ایک پین میں تیار کیاہوا بیف قیمہ لیں اوراس میں اُبلے ہوئے گارڈ الٹیمیٹ رائس ڈال دیں اور یہ عملدہرا کر دو تِہ بنا لیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں سبز دھنیا ،پودینہ ،لیموں ،سبز مرچ اور ٹماٹر کی گارنش کر لیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں پیلا رنگ ڈال کر دس منٹ تک دم دیں ۔\n
آپکی مزیدار بیف قیمہ بریانی تیار ہے ۔\n
</string>
    <string name="aalo">
کھانے کا تیل حسبِ ضرورت\n
اُبلے ہوئے آلو پانچ سو گرام\n
نمک	حسبِِ ذائقہ\n
لال مرچ کُٹی ہوئی ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
ہلدی پاؤڈر ایک چائے کاچمچ\n
دھنیا پاؤڈر	ایک چائے کا چمچ\n
زیرہ پاؤڈر	ایک چائے کا چمچ\n
ادرک پاؤڈر	ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
لیموں کا رس	دو کھانے کے چمچ\n
گُڑ ایک سو گرام\n
املی سوس	آدھا کپ\n
سبز مرچ دو عدد\n
سبز دھنیا پچاس گرام\n

۔ایک باؤل میں کھانے کا تیل لیں اوراس میں اُبلے ہوئے آلو ،نمک ،لال مرچ کُٹی ہوئی ،ہلدی ،دھنیا پاؤؑ ڈر ،زیرہ پاؤڈر ،ادرک پاؤڈر اور لیموں کا رس ڈال کر مکس کرلیں ۔\n
۔اب پین میں گُڑ لیں اوراس میں املی سوس ڈال کر مکس کرلیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں سبز مرچ اور سبز دھنیا ڈال کر مکس کرلیں اور پانچ منٹ پکالیں ۔\n
۔آپکے مزیدار کھٹے آلو تیار ہیں ۔\n
</string>
    <string name="afghani">افغانی پلائو بنانے کے اجزا\n
	700 گرامK and Ns Boti Cut\n
 اور K and Ns Chicken STOK  \n
باسمتی چاول	3 کپ\n
پیاز چوپ	2\n
ایلایچی پاؤڈر	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
زیرہ	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
لونگ	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
بڑی ایلایچی	2 عدد\n
دار چینی	2 عدد\n
سبز ایلایچی	5\n
زیرہ پاؤڈر	1 چائے کا چمچ\n
کالی مرچ پاؤڈر	1 چائے کا چمچ\n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ\n
لہسن چوپ	1کھانے کا چمچ\n
گاجر	1 کپ\n
کشمش	ایک چوتھائی کپ\n
چینی	ایک چوتھائی کپ\n
بادام	100 گرام\n
دہی	ایک کپ\n
کھانے کا تیل	آدھا کپ\n

افغانی پلائو بنانے کی ترکیب\n
ایک پین میں تین کھانے کے چمچ تیل لیں اس میں گاجر، چینی، کشمش، بادام ڈال کر تین سے چار منٹ تک پکا لیں۔ اور ایک بر تن میں الگ کر لیں۔\n
اب ایک پین میں تین کھانے کے چمچ کھانے کا تیل لیں اس میں پیاز، ادرک لہسن پیسٹ، گرم مصالحہ، ہری مرچ ڈال کر دو سے تین منٹ تک فرائی کر لیں۔ \n
اب K and Ns Chicken STOK اس میں ڈال کر پانچ سے سات منٹ تک فرائی کر لیں۔ \n
اب اس میں نمک، زیرہ پاؤڈر، دھنیاپاؤڈر، دہی، چینی ڈال کر اچھی طرح ملا لیں۔\n
اب اس میں سے فرائی کیا ہوا چکن نکال لیں۔اور تین کپ پانی ڈال دیں۔\n
اب K and Ns Chicken STOK اس میں ڈال کر تھوڑی دیر پکا لیں۔ \n
اب اس میں چاول ڈال کر دو سے تین منٹ تک پکا لیں۔
اب اس میں فرائی کیا ہوا چکن ڈال دیں اور دس سے پندرہ منٹ تک ڈھک کر دم دیں۔\n
اب اس میں فرائی کی ہوئی گاجر، بادام، کشمش ڈال کر دو منٹ تک دم دیں۔\n
اب اس کو ایک ٹرے میں نکال لیں اور اس پر فرائی کی ہوئی گاجر اور کشممش بادام سے گارنش کر لیں۔\n
آپکی مزے دار کابلی پلاؤ تیار ہے۔\n
پکانے کا وقت : 40 Minutes\n</string>
    <string name="qpatatha">
میدہ ڈیڑھ کپ\n
لال آٹا ایک کپ\n
مہران نمک حسبِ ذائقہ\n
گھی دو کھانے کے چمچ\n
نیم گرم پانی دو کھانے کے چمچ\n
کھانے کا تیل ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
مہران لہسن پیسٹ ٰٓایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
مہران ادرک پیسٹ ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
چکن قیمہ چھ سو گرام\n
مہران قیمہ مصالحہ دو کھانے کے چمچ\n
پیاز ایک عدد\n
سبز دھنیا پانچ گرام\n
پودینہ پانچ گرام\n
سبز مرچ دو عدد\n
مہران قصو ری میتھی ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
پسا ہوا انار دانہ ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n

ترکیب\n
۔ایک باؤل میں میدہ لیں اور اس میں لا ل آٹا ،نمک،گھی( ایک کھانے کا چمچ) اورنیم گرم پانی ڈال کر مکس کر کے اچھی طرح گوندھ لیں ۔\n
۔اب تیار شدہ آٹے کے پیڑے بنا کر تیس منٹ کے لیے ڈھانپ کر رکھ دیں ۔\n
۔اب ایک پین میں گھی ( ایک کھانے کا چمچ) لیں اور اس میں مہران لہسن پیسٹ ،مہران ادرک پیسٹ اور چکن قیمہ ڈال کر دو سے تین منٹ تک پکا لیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں مہران قیمہ مصالحہ ڈال کر پانچ منٹ تک بھونائی کر لیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں پیاز ،سبز دھنیا ،پودینہ ،سبز مرچ ،مہران قصوری میتھی اور پسا ہوا اناردانہ ڈال کر دو سے تین منٹ تک پکا لیں ۔\n
۔اب تیار شدہ پیڑوں کو بیلنے کی مدد سے بیل لیں۔\n
اب تیار شدہ قیمہ چپاتی پر پھیلا لیں اور دوسرے پیڑے کو بیل کر اس پر رکھ دیں اور سائیڈوں سے دبا کر بیل لیں ۔\n
۔اب ایک پین میں کھانے کا تیل لیں اور اس میں تیار شدہ چپاتی رکھ کر لائٹ براؤن ہونے تک پکا لیں ۔\n
آپکا مزیدار چکن قیمہ پراٹھا تیار ہے ۔\n
</string>
    <string name="imli">
اِملی پانچ سو گرام\n
پانی	تین کپ\n
چینی ایک کپ\n
لال مرچ ایک چائے کا چمچ\n

ترکیب : املی کی چٹنی\n
۔ایک باؤل میں پانی لیں اور اس میں املی کو ایک رات کے لیے بھگو لیں, گٹھلی نکال لیں ۔\n
۔اب املی کے گُدے کو پانی اور چینی میں ڈا ل کر پکا کر گاڑھا کر لیں ۔\n
\nآپکی مزیداراِملی کی چٹنی تیار ہے </string>
    <string name="muttonnehari">
کھانے کا تیل آدھا کپ\n
پیاز ڈیڑھ عدد\n
دہی ایک کپ\n
لہسن ادرکپیسٹ	دو کھانے کا چمچ\n
مٹن سات سو گرام\n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ\n
لال مرچ پاؤڈر ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
ہلدی پاؤڈر ایک چائے کا چمچ\n
تیار کیا ہوا نہاری مصالحہ تین کھانے کے چمچ\n
گرم مصالحہ پاؤڈر ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
گرم پانی دو کپ\n
ادرک دس گرام\n
سبز دھنیا دس گرام\n
سبز مر چ	چار عدد\n
لیموں بطور گارنش\n
گندم کا آٹا	تین کھانے کے چمچ\n
ترکیب\n
۔ایک پین میں کھانے کا تیل لیں اور اس میں پیاز ڈال کر گولڈن براؤن کرلیں ۔\n
۔اب ایک گرائینڈ ر میں دہی اور براؤن پیاز ڈال کر گرائینڈ کر لیں ۔\n
۔اب ایک پین میں کھانے کا تیل لیں اور اس میں ادرک لہسن پیسٹ اور مٹن ڈال کر دو سے تین منٹ تک پکالیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں نمک،لال مرچ پاؤڈر ،ہلدی ،تیار کیا ہوا نہاری مصالحہ ،گرم مصالحہ پاؤڈر ،تیار کیا ہوا پیاز اور دہی کا پیسٹ ڈال کر مکس کر لیں اور پانچ منٹ تک پکالیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں گرم پانی ڈال کر تیس سے پینتیس منٹ دم دیں ۔\n
۔اب ایک پین میں گندم کا آٹا لے کر بھون لیں اور پانی میں ملا کر مٹن میں ڈال دیں ۔\n
۔اب اسے پانچ منٹ تک دم دے کر ادرک ،سبز دھنیا ،سبز مرچ اور لیموں کی گارنش کر لیں ۔\n
۔آپکی مزیدار مٹن نہاری تیار ہے ۔\n
نہاری مصالحہ بنانے کا طریقہ\n
زیرہ تین کھانے کے چمچ\n
بادیان چار عدد\n
دارچینی	ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
دھنیا پاؤڈر ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
کالی مرچ پاؤڈر چھ عدد\n
ٹاٹر ی آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
تیز پات	ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
ہلدی ایک چائے کاچمچ\n
ادرک پاؤڈر آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
سبز الائچی چار عدد\n
بڑی الائچی چھ عدد\n
جیفل آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
جلوتری آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
سونف دو کھانے کے چمچ\n
۔سب چیزوں کو ایک گرائینڈر میں ڈال کر گرائینڈ کر لیں ۔\n
</string>
    <string name="kaleji">
سرکہ	دو کھانے کے چمچ\n
کھانے کا تیل آدھا کپ\n
پیاز دو عدد\n
ثابت زیرہ ایک چائے کا چمچ\n
ادرک لہسن پیسٹ تین کھانے کے چمچ\n
کلیجی ایک کلو\n
لال مر چ پاؤڈر	ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
ہلدی پاؤڈر ایک چائے کا چمچ\n
زیرہ پاؤڈر ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
دھنیا پاؤڈر ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
گرم مصالحہ پاؤڈر ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
ثابت گرم مصالحہ	ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
ٹماٹر چھ عدد\n
نمک	حسبِ ذائقہ\n
دہی ایک کپ\n
قصو ری میتھی ایک کھانے کا چمچ\n
سبز دھنیا پانچ گرام\n
ادرک پانچ گرام\n
سبز مر چ	چار عدد\n
مکھن	آدھا چائے کا چمچ\n
ترکیب\n
۔ایک باؤل میں کلیجی لیں اور اس میں سرکہ ادرک لہسن پیسٹ ڈال کر مکس کر لیں اور ایک گھنٹے کے لیے فریج میں رکھ دیں ۔\n
۔اب کلیجی کو ٹھنڈے پانی سے دھولیں ۔\n
۔اب ایک پین میں کھانے کا تیل لیں اورا س میں ثابت زیرہ ،پیازاورادرک لہسن پیسٹ ڈال کر لائٹ براؤن کر لیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں کلیجی ڈال کر آٹھ سے دس منٹ تک پکالیں ۔\n
۔اب ا س میں لال مرچ پاؤڈر ،ہلدی پاؤڈر ،زیرہ پاؤڈر ،دھنیا پاؤڈر گرم مصالحہ پاؤڈر ،ثابت گرم مصالحہ ڈال کر پانچ سے سات منٹ تک پکالیں ۔\n
۔ اب اس میں سبز مر چ،ٹماٹر ،نمک،دہی ڈال کر آٹھ سے دس منٹ تک پکالیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں قصوری میتھی ،سبز دھنیا ،ادرک اور سبز مر چ کی گارنش کر لیں ۔\n
اب اس میں سلور پیپر سے بنائی ہوئی کٹوری رکھیں اور سُلگتا ہوا کوئلہ اس میں رکھ دیں ۔\n
۔اب اس میں مکھن ڈال کر ڈھکنا بند کر دیں اور ایک منٹ بعد ہٹا دیں ۔\n
آپکی مزیدار سموک کلیجی تیار ہے ۔\n
</string>
    <string name="ind1">100 gms sear fish\n

50 gms coconut, grated\n

1/4 inch ginger\n

1/2 cup pureed tamarind\n

1 tsp salt\n

1/4 tsp powdered turmeric\n

2 small green chillies\n

1/2 tsp red chilli powder\n

2 tbsp shallots, finely chopped\n
       \n How to Make Malabari Fish Curry\n\n
1.Grind the coconut and turmeric powder with some water to form a fine paste.\n
2.Combine the tamarind extract, red chilli powder, ginger, salt and green chillies in a pan. Add the ground coconut paste and mix well. Place the pan over medium flame.\n
3.Simmer for two minutes. Add fish and salt. Cook for a few minutes till the mixture starts to harden.\n
4.Fry the tempering ingredients in coconut oil and add to the fish. Add the onions and stir gently. Remove after a minute. Serve hot with rice.\n

</string>
    <string name="ind2">6 pieces Medium Bitter Gourd (Karelay)\n
4 pieces medium Onions , sliced\n
3 gram Turmeric Powder\n
3 gram Red Chilli Powder\n
to taste Salt\n
2 tbsp Malt Vinegar\n
350 ml Mustard Oil\n
1 gram Carom Seeds/Bishops weed\n
5 gram Ginger\n
1 gram Asafoetida (Mixed in a little water)\n
1 tsp Amchoor\n
1 tsp Cumin Seed Powder\n
1 tsp Red Chilli Powder\n
1/2 tsp Saunf\n
1/2 tsp Black Pepper Powder\n
1/2 tsp Dried Fenugreek Leaf Powder\n
1 tsp Lemon Juice\n
\nHow to Make Aamchoori Kareley:n\n
1.Wash the bitter gourd and scrape the skin with a knife. Slit lengthwise, remove the seeds and slice thinly.\n
2.Transfer to a bowl, add turmeric, red chilli, salt and vinegar. Rub well with your hands to ensure that the gourd gets coated well with the spices.\n
3.Keep for 30 minutes, then wash in running water, shake dry and keep aside.\n
4.Add mustard oil in a wok, increase to high heat until the oil starts to smoke.\n
5.Reduce heat until smoking stops and oil reaches medium temperature. Fry the onions in the oil until golden brown, remove and transfer to absorbent paper to drain excess oil.\n
6.Now fry the bitter gourd in the same oil on medium high heat until it becomes crispy and golden brown. Remove and transfer to absorbent paper to remove the excess oil.\n
7.Transfer two tablespoons of the mustard oil used for frying to a wok and heat to medium heat.\n
8.Add carom seeds, stir well and add ginger along with asafoetida and keep stirring.\n
9.Increase the heat to high, add the bitter gourd, stir for a minute, then sprinkle mango, cumin, black pepper, red chilli, fennel and fenugreek powders.\n
10.Stir to mix well. Now add onions, stir, check the seasoning, add lemon juice, stir and remove from fire.\n
11.Transfer to a bowl and serve.\n

</string>

    <string name="ind3">1/4 Cup Ghee\n
1 Cup Cumin Seeds\n
1/8 tsp Asafoetida Water\n
1 tsp Ginger\n
2 Nos Tomato, pureed\n
1/2 tsp Garam Masala\n
1 tsp Coriander Powder\n
1/2 tsp Salt\n
1/2 tsp Turmeric Powder\n
1/2 tsp Red Chilli Powder\n
3-4 Potatoes (Boiled)\n
1 Green Chilli, chopped\n
1/2 Cup Water\n
1/2 Cup Curd\n
1/4 Cup Coriander Leaves\n
nHow to Make Dahi Aloo:\n\n
1.Take Ghee in a pan.\n
2.Add cumin seeds and asafoetida water to the pan.\n
3.Saute them and add ginger.\n
4.Mix the ginger along and add pureed tomato\n
5.Mix well and add garam masala, coriander powder, salt, turmeric powder and red chillli powder.\n
6.Mix the spices thoroughly.\n
7.Add boiled potatoes and green chilli to the gravy.\n
8.Mix all of it together.\n
9.Now add water and mix well.\n
10.Add curd to the cooked potato gravy.\n
11.Mix thoroughly till the gravy turns brownish-yellow in colour.\n
12.Add coriander leaves and mix well.\n
13.Serve hot.\n

    </string>
    <string name="ind4">2 Cups Oil\n
10 Aloo (Boiled)\n
1 Tbsp Oil\n
1 Cup Onion\n
1 tsp Ginger Garlic Paste\n
1/2 tsp Turmeric Powder\n
1/2 tsp Red Chilli Powder\n
1 tsp Achaar Masala\n
2 tsp Sugar\n
1 tsp Vinegar\n
1 Cup Water\n
For Tadka:\n
2 Tbsp Oil\n
1/2 tsp Mustard Seeds\n
1 tsp Cumin Seeds\n
1 tsp Kaloji\n
5 Whole Red Chilli\n
\n How to Make Achaari Aloo:\n\n
1.Take oil in a bowl and put aloo in it to deep fry.\n
2.Now in another pan of oil, add chopped onions.\n
3.Saute the onion till golden brown.\n
4.Add ginger garlic paste to the onion.\n
5.Now add turmeric powder, red chilli powder and achaar masala to the onion mix.\n
6.Mix them thoroughly.\n
7.Add boiled potatoes to the achaari masala mix.\n
8.Put sugar and Vinegar to the potatoes.\n
9.Mix them thoroughly.\n
10.Add water to the mix and cover the pan for a while and let it cook.\n
11.Remove the lid after a while\n
\nPrepare Tadka:\n\n
1.Take oil in a pan, add mustard seeds, cumin seeds, kalonji and whole red chillies.\n
2.Saute them well.\n
3.Pour the tadka over prepared aloo sabzi.\n
4.Serve Achaari Aloo hot.\n


</string>
    <string name="ind5">2 Tbsp Oil\n
1 Cup Bhindi\n
1 Onion, chopped\n
1 tsp Salt\n
1 tsp Turmeric Powder\n
1 tsp Red Chilli Powder\n
1 tsp Coriander Powder\n
1 tsp Cumin Powder\n
1 Cup Curd\n
2 Tbsp Ghee\n
1 tsp Mustard Seeds\n
1 tsp Urad Dal\n
10-12 Curry Leaves\n
2 Green Chillies\n
\n How to Make Dahi Aur Bhindi:\n\n
1.Take a cup full of Bhindi and put it in a hot pan with some oil for sautéing.\n
2.After bhindi, take onion in a hot oil pan and saute it till golden brown.\n
3.Now add the bhindi to this pan along with salt, , turmeric powder, red chilli powder, coriander powder and cumin powder.\n
4.Mix all the ingredients well and then add curd. Mix the curd well.\n
\n Prepare Tadka:\n\n
1.Pour some Ghee in the pan, add mustard seeds, urad dal, curry leaves and green chillies.\n
2.Saute the ingredients thoroughly.\n
3.Pour the tadka over the curry and mix it well.\n
4.Serve hot.\n
</string>
    <string name="ind6">500 Gram Maida\n
150 Gram Ghee\n
1.5 Litre Water\n
1 Litre Milk\n
50 Gram Sugar\n
5 Gram Cardamom powder\n
1 Gram Saffron\n
50 Gram Dry fruits, chopped\n
For sugar syrup:\n
500 Gram Sugar\n
250 Ml Water\n
A pinch of Saffron\n
For frying Ghee\n
\nHow to Make Malai Ghevar:\n\n
1.Heat Ghee in a heavy bottom pan and cool by adding ice, by this all the impurities are left behind and pure ghee gets accumulated on the surface.\n
2.Massage the ghee nicely till it is smooth and start incorporating the flour and water slowly till you get batter.\n
3.Heat ghee in a heavy bottom pan ,place a circular mold and start pouring the batter in center, fry till it is golden brown.\n
4.Make sugar syrup by heating water and sugar till the sugar dissolves completely.\n
5.Add the fried Ghevar to the warm syrup and remove.\n
6.To make malai heat milk,sugar ,cardamom powder and saffron and reduce to half,cool till it thickens.\n
7.Top the malai on the ghevar and garnish with chopped nuts.\n
</string>
    <string name="ind7">2 Cups whole wheat flour\n
A pinch of salt\n
1 tbsp oil\n
2 Eggs\n
1/4 cup onions, chopped\n
1 green chilli, chopped\n
2 tbsp coriander leaves, chopped\n
1/2 tsp garam masala\n

\nHow to Make Egg Paratha:\n\n
1.In a mixing bowl, add flour, salt and oil, and knead the mixture into a smooth dough using 1 cup of water. You can add in a little more water if the dough seems dry. Knead well.\n
2.Divide the dough into 4 balls.\n
3.Roll out the dough ball evenly using a rolling pin, then fold it twice to form a triangle. Roll it out again to make a triangular sheet. Repeat the process with the remaining dough.\n
4.In a bowl, whisk the eggs well along with onions, chilli, coriander leaves, garam masala and salt. Keep aside.\n
5.Place the rolled dough on a hot tawa, and let it cook for 1-2 minutes on both sides. Add a little oil on the surface and let it cook for one more minute.\n
6.As the edges start to crisp, quickly make a slit using a sharp knife along the folds and pour in half the quantity of egg. Tilt the paratha a little so that the egg mix slides in. Then flip it over and repeat the process on the other side.\n
7.Drizzle some more oil on the paratha and press the surface gently using the back of your spoon. Turn up the heat and continue cooking the paratha until it fluffs up and turns crisp brown.\n
8.Serve hot with a helping of desi ghee on top.\n</string>
    <string name="ind8">100 gms cottage cheese\n
40 gms singhare ka atta (water chestnut flour)\n
to taste sendha namak\n
200 gms fresh tomato puree\n
5 gms ajwain (caraway seed)\n
20 gms deggi mirch\n
10 gms coriander, chopped\n
100 ml oil\n
\n How to Make Ajwaini Paneer Kofta Curry:\n\n
Prepare kofta:\n
1.Mash the cottage cheese and add singare ka atta and senda namak.\n
2.Make roundels and fry in oil.\n
Prepare gravy:\n
1.Remove the eye ,then boil the tomatoes ,make puree and stain.\n
2.In a pan heat oil and add ajwain and sauté for a minute. Then add the stained tomato puree and cook for 5 minutes.\n
3.Add the deggi mirch and sendha namak .\n
4.Then add fried kofta in the gravy and serve hot garnished with coriander.\n

</string>
    <string name="ind9">
15-20 Saffron strands\n
50 ml cold milk\n
500 gms yogurt\n
100 gms powdered sugar\n
1 tsp cardamom powder\n
for garnishing dry fruit slivers\n
\nHow to Make Kesari Shrikhand:\n\n
1.Soak saffron in milk for 3-4 hours.\n
2.Add yogurt, powdered sugar, cardamom powder and saffron milk together. Mix well.\n
3.Transfer the shrikhand in the serving bowls.\n
4.Garnish with slivered dry fruits.\n
5.Chill in the refrigerator before serving.\n</string>
    <string name="ind10">1.5 Litre milk\n
150 sugar\n
50 pistachio\n
0.2 saffron\n
50 thandai syrup\n
\nHow to Make Thandai Barfi:\n\n
1.Take full fat milk in thick bottom pan, add sugar, and start boiling it.\n
2.Stir well on slow flame so that in doesn’t burn from bottom.\n
3.Stir till it becomes thick like milk solid called mawa.\n
4.Add thandai syrup, chopped pistachio and saffron.\n
5.Flattened the hot barfi on greased aluminium tray.\n
6.Garnish barfi with saffron.\n
7.Cut into 1 inch squares and serve cold.\n</string>
    <string name="ind11">200 gms paneer\n
2 ginger, grated\n
1/2 tsp turmeric powder\n
1/2 tsp chilli powder\n
1/2 tsp garam masala powder\n
1 tomato\n
1/2 cup water\n
2 stalks coriander leaves\n
2 pinches powdered black pepper\n
4 tbsp refined oil\n
3 onion, chopped\n
1/2 cup beaten curd\n
\nHow to Make Handi Paneer:\n\n
1.Put oil in a handi, stir fry the chopped onions on medium flame, when done, reduce the flame to low. Then add two pieces of grated ginger, turmeric powder, chilli powder, garam masala and mix well.\n
2.Add the finely chopped tomato and green chilli, and cook on low flame for about 10 minutes.\n
3.Add half cup beaten curd and cook till dry, before adding salt. Add half cup water and bring it to a boil.\n
4.Mix in malai paneer and chopped coriander, cook till the masala dries.\n
5.Add pepper and remove from the flame. Serve in a large bowl and sprinkle coriander leaves over the dish.\n</string>
    <string name="ind12">
300 gms chicken mince\n
50 gms onion, chopped\n
50 gms tomatoes, chopped\n
50 gms green capsicum, chopped\n
30 gms coriander leaves, chopped\n
20 gms green chilli, chopped\n
5 gms salt\n
20 ml oil\n
20 gms cashew\n
20 gms almonds, peeled\n
10 gms mint, chopped\n
5 gms red chilli powder\n
5 gms masala powder\n
5 gms ginger garlic paste\n
3 gms cumin powder\n
10 ml lemon juice\n
10 ml fresh cream\n
5 ml kewra water\n
\nHow to Make Chicken Gilafi Kebab:\n\n
1.In a grinder add mince, onion, salt, red chili powder, garam masala, ginger garlic paste, cumin powder, lemon juice, coriander leaves, mint leave, green chilies, fresh cream, kewra water, cashew and almonds.\n
2.Grind all these ingredients well.\n
3.Skewer the mince on to wooden skewers.\n
4.Take chopped onion, capsicum and coriander leaves in a flat plate.\n
5.Wrap these chopped vegetables around the kebabs.\n
6.Bake them in oven at 180 degree for 8 to 10 minutes.\n
7.Your Gilafi kebabs are ready to serve.\n

</string>
    <string name="ind13">
For the Tart\n
500 gms white butter\n
250 gms breakfast sugar\n
100 ml milk full fat\n
750 gms refined flour\n
For Gajar ka Halwa\n
1 kg winter carrots\n
200 gms ghee\n
90 gms sugar\n
200 gms khoya\n
5 gms cardamom powder\n
50 gms cashew nuts (crushed), fried\n
50 gms almonds (crushed), fried\n
400 ml full fat milk\n
For Rabdi\n
full fat milk\n
grain sugar\n
green cardamom powder\n
How to Make Gajar Halwa Tart\n
\nFor the tarts:\n\n
1.Cream butter and sugar together till light and fluffy, adding milk gradually.\n
2.Add the flour and mix thoroughly.\n
3.Let the sweet paste rest in the refrigerator for at least 6 hours.\n
For the carrot halwa:\n
1.Heat the ghee in a heavy bottomed pan and add grated carrots.\n
2.Cook till the carrots are soft and moisture has been drained out. Add the sugar and cook further.\n
3.Add full fat milk to the carrots and reduce over slow heat.\n
4.Add the cardamom powder and nuts and khoya and cook over medium flame for further 20-25 minutes.\n
For Rabdi:\n
1.Take full fat milk in a thick bottom pan and reduce over medium heat until reduced to ¼ of the original quantity. Add sugar and mix well.\n
2.Cook for another 5-10 minutes until sugar dissolves.\n
3.Once done, remove from flame and add green cardamom powder. Let it cool, cream butter and sugar together till light and fluffy, adding milk gradually.\n
</string>
    <string name="ind14">Cooking oil\n
Whole chicken (skin on- rinsed and dressed)\n
2-3 Onions (quartered- skin on)\n
1 bulb Garlic (halved - skin on)\n
4-5 Carrots (roughly quartered)\n
1/2 Cup Celery , finely chopped\n
5 sprigs Thyme\n
250 Ml Dunkleweizen (pour into a glass and keep open at room temperature for an hour or two to make flat)\n
2 Cups Chicken stock\n
3 Tbsp Butter\n
To taste Sea salt\n
\nHow to Make Half Roast Chicken:\n\n
1.Preheat oven to 220 degree C.\n
2.In a greased oven tray line the carrots, celery, onions, garlic and thyme.\n
3.Place the chicken on the tray and grease with oil and sprinkle with sea salt.\n
4.Roast the chicken for 1.5 hours or till the juices run clear. Remove from the tray and reserve/rest.\n
5.While the chicken is resting, pour the dunkelweizen into the tray turn the oven to the highest heat setting and let it bubble for five minutes.\n
6.Remove the tray from the oven and transfer all contents to a sauce pan before adding in the chicken stock and the butter.\n
7.Reduce the mixture of the beer, and chicken stock till it coats a spoon, adjust the salt.\n
8.Serve with buttery mashed potatoes.\n</string>
    <string name="ind15">300 Gram Chicken leg B/L\n
5 Gram Green chilli\n
1 Small Elaichi\n
1 Elaichi\n
1 Cinnamon sticks\n
1 Gram Mace\n
1 Bay leaf\n
1 Javitri\n
1 Gram Cloves\n
1 Kg Basmati rice\n
To taste Salt\n
3 Gram Shahi jeera\n
50 Ml Desi ghee\n
20 Gram Ginger
20 Gram Garlic\n
0.1 Gram Saffron\n
100 Gram Onion\n
50 Gram Butter\n
10 Gram Mint\n
10 Gram Garam masala\n
30 Gram Red chilli powder\n
\nHow to Make Murgh Biryani:\n\n
1.Wash chicken leg B/L and pet dry. marinate with ginger, garlic paste, curd and garam masala. Keep aside.\n
2.Soak basmati rice for 20 minutes.\n
3.Take thick bottom pan, put all whole spices, slices of onion, cook till brown, add marinated chicken and cook for 5 minutes.\n
4.Boil rice in salt and mint flavoured water.\n
5.Add chicken in pre cooked rice.\n
6.Cover with lid and cook till the steam comes out. Check seasoning.\n
7.Serve hot with raita.\n</string>
    <string name="ind16">For mutton:\n
750 Gram Boneless meat (cleaned and washed)\n
8 Green chillies\n
1 tsp Ginger garlic paste\n
1/2 tsp Turmeric powder\n
3-4 Cinnamon stick\n
4 Cloves\n
2-3 Green cardamom\n
1 tsp Caraway seeds (shahi zeera)\n
1 Tbsp Black peppercorns\n
To taste Salt\n
1 Cup Water\n
For cooking dals:\n
1/2 Cup Dalia (broken wheat)\n
1 tsp Mash ki dal/Urad dal\n
1 tsp Toovar dal\n
1 tsp Chana dal\n
1 tsp Yellow moong dal\n
1 tsp Rice\n
To taste Salt\n
3 glasses Water\n
Other ingredients:\n
3 Tbsp Oil\n
4 Medium Onions, sliced\n
1 tsp Ginger garlic paste\n
1/2 Coriander leaves, chopped\n
1/2 Mint leaves, chopped\n
2 Green chillies (slit)\n
1/2 Black pepper corn powder\n
1/4 Turmeric powder\n
1 1/2 Yogurt (beaten)\n
5-6 Tbsp Pure ghee\n
For garnishing:\n
Coriander leaves, chopped\n
Mint leaves, chopped\n
Onions, fried\n
5-6 Lemons (cut into 4 halves)\n
\nHow to Make Haleem Khowsuey:\n\n
Prepare the mutton:\n
1.Firstly, in a cooking pot, add the mutton chunks, about 8 green chillies, ginger garlic paste.\n
2.Add whole spices such as cloves, cardamoms, cinnamon, caraway seeds, black pepper corns.\n
3.Add salt as per taste, add turmeric powder.\n
4.Add little water (1 glass approximately), mix well and cook the mutton until it is tender.\n
\nPrepare the dals:\n\n
1.Take a cooking pot, into it add daliya/broken wheat, add urad dal, add toovar dal, add chana dal, add yellow moong dal and rice.\n
2.Add about 3 glasses of water and pressure cook until the dals get soft.\n
\nBlending the mutton and dals:\n\n
1.In a blender, add the cooked mutton and blend into a fine paste and transfer it into a bowl or vessel.\n
2.In the same blender, add the cooked dals and blend into a fine paste and keep aside.\n
\nMixing the cooked mutton and dals:\n\n
1.In a separate cooking pot, add oil, add 4 medium size sliced onions and fry until golden brown.\n
2.Add ginger garlic paste and saute well.\n
3.Add fresh coriander leaves, mint leaves, green chillies, mix well.\n
4.Add black pepper corn powder, turmeric powder and mix well.\n
5.Add beaten yogurt, mix and cook for 5 minutes on low flame.\n
6.Add the blended paste of dals and also the blended paste of mutton into it.\n
7.Mix it well and keep stirring and mixing until the mutton and dals get mixed well evenly.\n
8.Add the mutton stock and mix well.\n
9.Now add pure ghee all over and mix.\n
10.Cover the lid and cook it for about 15 minutes on low flame.\n
11.Remove the lid and give a mix.\n
12.Switch off the flame.\n
13.Haleem is ready to serve\n</string>
    <string name="ind17">200 Gram Bajra flour\n
100 Gram Wheat flour\n
250 Gram Fenugreek leaves\n
2 Garlic cloves, finely chopped\n
1 Tbsp Low fat curd\n
1 Green chilli, chopped\n
50 Gram Low fat paneer\n
2 tsp Coriander leaves, chopped\n
1/2 tsp Haldi powder\n
1/2 tsp Red chilli powder\n
To taste Salt\n
\nHow to Make Bajra-Methi Missi Roti\:n\n
1.Combine all the ingredients and knead into firm dough with required amount of water.\n
2.Divide into five portions. Roll out into thin rotis and roast on a tawa till they are well done.\n
3.Serve hot with green chutney.\n</string>
    <string name="ind18">200 Gram Arbi\n
50 gram Cashew\n
2 nos Green chillies\n
to taste Sendha namak\n
100 ml Ghee\n
To garnish Fresh coriander\n
\nHow to Make Arbi Kaju Ki Tikki:\n\n
1.Boil arbi by adding a pinch of sendha namak.\n
2.Make cashew nut paste.\n
3.Mash arbi and mix with cashew paste, green chilly and ghee.\n
4.Make small tikki’s out of the above mix and shallow fry it on a flat pan.\n
5.Fry till golden brown and serve with yogurt and cucumber dip.\n</string>
    <string name="ind19">Cloves\n
Cardamom\n
Cinnamon\n
Star Anise\n
Water\n
Tea leaves\n
Sugar\n
Milk\n

\nHow to Make Masala Chai:\n\n
1.Roast the spices like cloves, cinnamon, cardamom and star anise together in equal amounts in a pan.\n
2.Grind the roasted ingredients together to get a powder.\n
3.In a wok full of boiling water, put the ground mixture along with the other remaining ingredients.\n
4.Stir and bring it to simmer.\n
5.Serve hot along with some tea-time munchies.\n
    </string>
    <string name="ind20">1 Kg mutton\n
2 tbsp refined oil\n
3-4 Green cardamom\n
1 tsp whole cinnamon\n
2 Black cardamoms\n
2-3 Bay leaves\n
1 tsp turmeric powder\n
1/4 cup water\n
1 tsp ginger-garlic paste\n
1 tsp coriander powder\n
1 tsp red chilli powder\n
1 tsp garlic (ground), fried\n
1 tsp onion (ground), fried\n
3 tbsp yogurt (beaten)\n
2 tsp gulab jal\n
2 tsp garam masala\n
1/2 tsp nutmeg-coriander powder\n
1/2 tsp saffron, soaked\n
to taste salt\n
Few drops of ittar\n
Wheat dough (for dum)\n
for garnishing fresh coriander\n
for garnishing ginger, julienne\n
\nHow to Make Awadhi Gosht Korma:\n\n
1.Heat oil in a pan and add green cardamom, cinnamon, cloves, black cardamom and bay leaves.\n
2.Add the meat and saute till lightly fried.\n
3.Add salt and turmeric and mix well.\n
4.Pour in the water, cover the pan and cook.\n
5.When it starts boiling, add ginger- garlic paste, coriander powder, red chilli, garlic paste and onion paste.\n
6.Mix well and add yogurt, gulab-jal, garam masala, nutmeg and cinnamon powder and saffron.\n
7.Cover and cook for 2-3 minutes.\n
8.Now transfer the meat in a heavy bottom pan and strain the gravy.\n
9.Add a few drops of ittar and cover the pan.\n
10.Seal it with the wheat dough and cook on slow fire.\n
11.Once done, garnish with fresh coriander and ginger juliennes and serve.\n</string>


    <string name="a1">Whole chicken 1\n
Yogurt 1 cup\n
Ginger, garlic paste 2 tbsp\n
Vinegar 4 tbsp\n
Black pepper powder ½ tsp\n
Cumin powder 1 tsp\n
Funnel seeds 1 tsp\n
Pomegranate seeds 1 tsp\n
Whole red chili 8\n
Dry mango powder 1 tsp\n
Green cardamom 1 pod\n
Salt to taste\n
\nMethod:\n\n
Dry roast whole spices then grind into powder.\n

In a small bowl mix all ingredients.\n

Apply cuts on chicken and coat masala on chicken nicely. Leave it over night or at least 5 hours in fridge.\n

Add ¼ cup water in a skillet, place chicken. Cover and cook on slow heat until chicken tender and water dries.\n

Now place chicken in a baking tray, spread remaining masala on it and bake in hot oven for five minutes or place on coal fire.\n

Serve delicious Arabic chicken sajji with hot naan or taftan and mint dip.\n
</string>
    <string name="a2">Mutton 1 kg (pieces)\n
Cinnamon powder 1 tsp\n
Corn flour 2 tbsp\n
Garlic clove 3 – 4\n
Paprika powder 2 tbsp\n
Onion 2\n
Chicken powder 2 tbsp\n
Chicken stock 1 jug\n
Fresh coriander/parsley ½ bunch\n
Oil ½ cup\n
Salt to taste\n
\nMethod:\n\n
Wash meat and marinate it with salt, paprika powder and 1/2 tsp cinnamon powder.\n

Leave it for a while.\n

Now crush the onion and garlic.\n

Heat oil in a pan and add onion, garlic, chicken powder and 1 cup chicken stock.\n

Cook for 10 – 15 minutes.\n

When stock becomes dry, stir fry it well.\n

Now add meat and fry it again.\n

When meat fried well then add remaining chicken stock and cook for 2-3 minutes.\n

Now add remaining 1/2 tsp cinnamon powder and cook 10 minutes more.\n

When meat is tender then take it out and keep aside.\n

Now add corn flour in remaining curry, mix well and make it thick like stew.\n

Now strain and combine the meat mixture.\n

Garnish with coriander leaves.\n

</string>
    <string name="a3">Bread slice 8 – 10
Evaporated milk 1 tin
Almond 10 - 12
Dry apricot 10
Small cardamom 4
Oil as required
Corn flour 2 tsp
Sugar ½ cup
Orange marmalade 2 tbsp
Silver paper as required
\nMethod:\n\n
 Cut slices in 2 - 4 pieces.\n

Take out almond from apricot.\n

Cut apricot and almond in small pieces.\n

Now crush cardamom with 1 tbsp of sugar.\n

Heat up oil in a wok and put slices to fry till it turns golden brown and spread it on absorbing paper.\n

Take another frying pan and add evaporated milk, corn flour and cardamom and make a thick batter.\n

Melt sugar and make caramel and put almond and apricot in it.\n

When chill out add marmalade in it.\n

Now first place the fried pieces of bread.\n

Then place layer of milk batter and in the end place layer of apricot.\n

Garnish it with silver paper.\n
</string>
    <string name="a4">For Dough:\n\n
Flour 2 cups\n
Salt ½ tsp\n
Milk as required (to knead)\n
\nFor Filling:\n\n
Mince 300 gm\n
Ginger garlic paste 1 tsp\n
Salt ½ tsp\n
Chinese salt ½ tsp\n
Black pepper ½ tsp\n
Fresh coriander ½ bunch\n
Green chilies 4\n
Spring onion 1\n
Egg 2\n
Clarified butter for fry\n
\nFor cooking Eggs:\n\n
Black pepper ½ tsp\n
Salt ¼ tsp\n
Oil 2 tbsp\n
\nMethod:\n\n
\n For Dough:\n\n

Mix together flour, salt and knead to a dough with milk.

\nFor Filling:\n\n

In a pan, cook mince with ginger garlic paste, salt and water.

Cook till water evaporates and mince is tender.

Now add Chinese salt, black pepper, coriander, chopped spring onion and chopped green chilies.

Mix well and turn the flame off.

Separately beat eggs with black pepper and salt.

Now heat oil and fry egg mixture in it.

\nFor Paratha:\n\n

Make balls of dough.

Roll and spread mince filling on it.

Now spread egg filling and cover it from all sides.

Again roll and fry on Tawa with clarified butter.
</string>
    <string name="a5">Coloured vermicelli 200 grams\n
Milk 2 litres\n
Sugar 250 grams\n
Saffron colour ¼ tsp\n
Clarified butter 100 grams\n
Almonds 10 (sliced)\n
Pistachios 10 (sliced)\n
Raisins 10 grams\n
Dates 100 grams (sliced)\n
Green cardamoms 3\n
Cinnamon sticks 2\n
Cloves 3\n
Screw pine essence a few drops\n
\nMethod:\n\n
Heat clarified butter in a pan and add the cinnamon sticks, cloves, green cardamoms, dates, almonds, pistachios, raisins and coloured vermicelli.\n

Stir continuously and then add the milk and cook on medium flame.\n

Now add the sugar, saffron color and screw pine essence and cook until the mixture begins to boil.\n

Serve warm or cold.\n
</string>
    <string name="a6">Chicken (cut into small pieces)-1 kg\n
Rice (washed and soaked for 20 minutes)-1 kg\n
Salt as per taste\n
Garlic Paste-1 tbsp\n
Red Chillies-1 tbsp\n
Cloves	6-8\n
Small Cardamom	6-8\n
Bay Leaves	1-2\n
Green Chillies (chopped) 3-4\n
Capsicum (cubed)-2 medium\n
Hot Sauce-2 tbsp\n
\nMethod:\n\n
In a pot, heat Cooking oil on medium heat for 3-4 minutes.\n

Add Cloves,cardamom and bay leaves and stir fry for 1-2 minutes.\n

Add garlic,salt and chicken and mix well.\n

Cover and cook on medium heat until water in the chicken dries.\n

When the water dries,add rice and stir well for a few minutes.\n

Add 4 cups of water and mix well.\n

Cook on medium heat until only 1/2 cup water remain.\n

Add green and red chillies and cook until the water dries.\n

Then add capsicum and hot sauce and simmer on low heat for 5-7 minutes.\n

Mix well and dish out.Serve with hot sauce.\n
Cooking Oil\n</string>
    <string name="a7">Rice ½ kg\n
Meat ½ kg\n
Tomato paste 1 cup\n
Onion 1\n
Salt 2 tsp\n
Oil 1 cup\n
White cumin 1 tsp\n
Green Cardamom 10 pods\n
Black Pepper 12 pods\n
Cinnamon 1 piece\n
Kabuli Chickpeas 1 cup (boiled)\n
Carrot 1 cup (grated)\n
Bay leaf 2 leaves
\nMethod:\n\n
In a pan, brown the onions then remove from oil and crush.\n

Add meat in same oil and fry until changes the color.\n

Add the tomato paste and crushed onions.\n

Grind the white cumin, green cardamom, black pepper, cinnamon and wrap them up in cloth to make a spice bag.\n

Add the spice bag and 6 cups of water in the pan.\n

Add the bay leafs and cook until the meat is tender and 1 glass stock left then add the grated carrot.\n

Add rice and kabuli chickpeas. Allow to cook for 5 minutes.\n

Keep on steam for 30 minutes. Your dish is ready and served hot.\n</string>
    <string name="a8">Baqarkhani 150 gm\n
Milk 2 cups\n
Sugar 4 tbsp\n
Almonds 56 gm (crushed)\n
Walnuts 56 gm (crushed)\n
Raisins 56 gm\n
Desiccated coconut 28 gm\n
Cream 1 cup (whipped)\n
\nMethod:\n\n
Heat milk and add sugar.\n

Cook till sugar dissolves and then remove.\n

Break baqarkhanis and spread in a pyrex dish.\n

Layer with almonds, walnuts, raisins and desiccated coconut.\n

Gently pour milk over it.\n

Spread cream on top.\n

Bake in pre-heated oven at 180°c for 25 minutes and remove.\n

Serve warm.\n
</string>
    <string name="a9">For Dough:\n\n
All purpose flour 2 cups\n
Salt 1 tsp\n
Milk as required\n
\nFor Frying:\n\n
Egg 1 for each murtabak\n
Tomatoes (chopped) as required\n
Allspice powder as required\n
Spring onion (finely chopped) as required\n
\nFor Mince:\n\n
Mince 250 gm\n
Oil 2 tbsp\n
Ginger and garlic paste 1 tsp\n
Salt 1 tsp\n
Chinese salt 1/2 tsp\n
Black pepper 1/2 tsp\n
Coriander leaves as required\n
Mint leaves as required\n
Green chillies as required\n
\nMethod:\n\n
For Mince: Heat oil and add mince, salt, Chinese salt, black pepper, ginger and garlic paste.\n

Then cook until water dries.\n

Sprinkle coriander leaves, mint and green chillies.\n

For Dough: Kneed flour with milk until the dough is smooth, divide into 30 equal balls.\n

Apply oil on top and leave aside for 15 minutes.\n

Apply oil on a marble top or a smooth surface and rollout one ball of the dough.\n

For Frying: Spread prepared mince, sprinkle allspice, chopped tomatoes and spring onions.\n

Break an egg on top and fold sides so that a square is formed.\n

Fry on medium heat till golden on both sides.\n
</string>
    <string name="a10">Water 1 jug\n
Figs 8-10\n
Almonds 10-12\n
Sugar 3-4 tbsp\n
Bananas 3\n
Apricot 3\n
Red drink (jam-e-sheerin) 1 small bowl\n
\nMethod:\n\n
Soak figs in water overnight.\n

Peel off the almonds.\n

Blend together water, red drink and sugar.\n

Pour it in the glasses.\n

Now add equal quantities of almonds and figs in each glass.\n

Slice the apricots in half.\n

Add 1 apricot in each glass.\n

Now slice the bananas and add 1 full banana slices in each glass.\n
</string>
    <string name="a11">Chicken cubes 500 gm\n
Yogurt ¼ cup\n
Oil 4 tbsp\n
Garlic paste 2 tbsp\n
Lemon juice 1 tbsp\n
Thyme ¼ tsp\n
Oregano ¼ tsp\n
All spice mixture ¼ tsp\n
Cumin powder ½ tsp\n
Salt 1 tsp\n
Black pepper powder ½ tsp\n
Tomato paste 1 tbsp\n
Onion 1\n
Tomato 1\n
Capsicum 1\n
Bamboo skewer 8- 10\n
\nMethod:\n\n
Put chicken cubes, yogurt, oil, garlic paste, lemon juice, thyme, oregano, all spice mixture, cumin powder, salt, black pepper powder and tomato paste in bowl and keep to marinate.\n

Place one piece of chicken, onion, tomato and capsicum on single bamboo skewer and then grill them.\n

Delicious Shish tauk is ready to serve.\n
</string>
    <string name="a12">All purpose flour 2 cups\n
Salt ½ tsp\n
Milk as required (for knead)\n
\nFor Filling:\n\n
Mince 300 gm\n
Ginger and garlic paste ½ tsp\n
Salt ½ tsp\n
Chinese salt ½ tsp\n
Black pepper ½ tsp\n
Fresh coriander ½ bunch (crushed)\n
Green chilies 2 (chopped)\n
Spring onion 1 (finely chopped)\n
Eggs 2\n
Oil for frying\n
\nFor Egg Filling\n\n
Black pepper ½ tsp\n
Salt ¼ tsp\n
Oil 2 tbsp\n
\nMethod:\n\n
For Dough:\n\n

Mix together flour, salt and knead to make dough with milk.\n

\nFor Filling:\n\n

In a pan, cook mince with ginger garlic paste, salt and water.\n

Cook till water evaporates and mince is tender.\n

Now add Chinese salt, black pepper, coriander, chopped spring onion and chopped green chilies.\n

Mix well and turn the flame off.\n

Separately beat 2 eggs with black pepper and salt.\n

Now heat oil and fry egg mixture in it.\n

\nFor Paratha:\n\n

Make balls of dough.\n

Roll and spread mince filling on it.\n

Now spread egg filling and cover it from all sides.\n

Again roll and fry on Tawa.\n
Serve hot with raita.\n</string>
    <string name="a13">Pasta ½ packet\n
Spring onion green part 1 cup\n
Green coriander ½ cup (chopped)\n
Spinach 1 cup finely chopped (optional)\n
Oregano 1 tbsp\n
Olive oil 2 tbsp\n
Salt to taste\n
\nMethod:\n\n
Wash and clean all vegetables chop green coriander, spring onion and spinach very finely on cutting board.\n

In a bowl add chopped spring onion, spinach, boiled pasta, olive oil, oregano, and salt.\n

Mix all with spoon dish out and serve.\n</string>
    <string name="a14">Raw peanuts 1/2 kg\n
Gram flour (besan) 1/2 kg\n
Salt to taste\n
Black pepper 1 tsp\n
Chaat spice as required\n
\nMethod:\n\n
Take a bowl and mix gram flour, salt and black pepper in it.\n

Add water and make a thick mixture.\n

Now add peanuts.\n

Deep fry in oil till crisp and golden.\n

Sprinkle chaat spice on it and serve hot.\n
    </string>
    <string name="a15">Chicken legs 2\n
Chicken breasts	2\n
Rice 2 cups\n
Clarified butter 1 cup\n
Onion 2 (chopped)\n
White vinegar 2 tbsp\n
Small cardamom 6 (chopped)\n
Yogurt ½ cup\n
Ginger garlic paste 1 tbsp\n
Almonds 10 (boiled, chopped)\n
Raisins 1 cup\n
Green chilies 4\n
Salt to taste\n
\nMethod:\n\n
Wash and soak the rice.\n

Heat some clarified butter in the pan and add in chopped onion.\n

Fry it till they are golden brown.\n

Take the onion and add in the chicken pieces.\n

Cook it till the water dries.\n

Add in salt, green chilies white vinegar, small cardamom, yogurt and ginger garlic paste. Cook it.\n

Add in almonds and raisins.\n

Cook it and add in 2 – 3 cups of water and rice in it to cook.\n

When it boils and simmer it.\n

Take the rice out, garnish fried onion and serve hot.\n</string>
    <string name="a16">Chicken 8 pieces\n
Rice 3 cup (soaked)\n
Water 2 liter\n
Salt to taste\n
Pure butter 4 tbsp\n
Potato 2 medium (medium cubed)\n
Onion 250 gm (sliced)\n
Cinnamon 2 sticks\n
Whole black pepper 5\n
Cloves 5\n
Coriander powder 1 tsp\n
Black pepper powder 1 tsp\n
Red chili powder ½ tsp\n
All spice powder ½ tsp\n
Tomato 2 (sliced)\n
Tomato paste 3 tbsp\n
\nFor Garnishing:\n\n
Almonds 10 (blanched and peeled)\n
Cashews 10\n
Raisins 20 (fry all in 1tbsp butter)\n
\nMethod:\n\n
Add water, chicken pieces and salt in a pot and allow boiling and remove froth as it appears.\n

Cover pot and cook about 20 minutes or until chicken cooked.\n

Remove chicken from stock and set aside. Reserve stock.\n

In another pot melt pure butter and fry chicken pieces from all sides until get a brownish color. Remove chicken and set aside again.\n

In same butter fry potato for 3 minutes then add sliced onion and fry until onion golden brown.\n

Add spices, tomatoes and tomato puree; mix well.\n
Pour stock, it should be around 6 cups.\n

Add rice, cover and cook until rice 80% done.\n

Now place chicken pieces on top of rice and simmer about 10 minutes.\n

Dish out rice, garnish with nuts and serve.\n
</string>
    <string name="a17">2 cup all-purpose flour\n
1/2 cup Semolina\n
1/4 cup sugar\n
3 cup water\n
2 tbsp Baking powder\n
2 tbsp Suger\n
1 cup Goat cheese(or any sweet or unflavored cheese)\n
1/2 liter vegetable oil(for frying)\n
2 cup sugar\n
2 cup water\n
1 tbsp lemon juice\n
\nSteps:\n\n

Put the sugar and the water and boil them, put the lemon juice and boil the syrup for 10 minutes, remove it until cool.\n


Mix all of the ingredients in the mixer.\n


Preheat a pan , then put some of the mixed ingredients in it (the same way you make pancakes) until you see all the bubbles remove it, and put it on a baking sheet.\n


On a side dish put the goat cheese(make it like crumbs) with suger.\n


Put the cheese inside the qatayf (pancakes) and close it will be like a half moon.\n


Preheat another pan with oil , fri the qatayf until its golden.\n


Put them right away in the sugar syrup , remove them and shake the extra syrup , put them on a plate and serve.\n</string>
    <string name="a18">5 chopped onions.\n
2 large potatos sliced up.\n
1 olive oil.\n
1 egg plant chopped up.\n
1 chopped tomato\n
1 tbsp ginger powder seasoning you can also use fresh ground up ginger.\n
2 green chilli pepprs cut up.\n
2 garlic gloves chopped.\n
1 kg sheep meat.\n
1 salt and pepper a few dashes.\n
1/4 cup ketchup.\n
1 chopped carrot.\n
4 dash cummin powder.\n
1 cup tomatoe paste.\n
2 dash curry powder.\n
4 dash coriander powder.\n
2 dash chilli powder.\n
\nSteps:\n\n
Get a big cooking pot to cook on stove with.\n


Olive oil pour just enough in pan to cover bottom of pan.\n


Tenderize all the vegetables in the oil.\n


Cook sheep meat in a separate pan covered in water with a few dashes of salt and pepper seasoning.\n


After the meat is done drain water off meat. Add The sheep meat to The vegetable mixture.\n


Add 8 cups of water to it the vegetables and meat mixture.\n


Add tomatoe paste and the remaining seasoning to the mixture and let simmer on low Heat for 20 Minutes covered.\n</string>
    <string name="a19">2 tablespoons arabic coffee\n
3 tablespoons ground cardamom, powder\n
1/4 teaspoon saffron\n
\nSteps:	\n\n

Put 3 cups of water in a pot and bring to a boil.\n


Add the coffee and boil over low flame. Turn the heat off after 5 minutes and leave the coffee to clear.\n


Pour the coffee into a kettle, leaving the coffee to settle in the pot.\n


Add in the cardamom and saffron to the kettle of coffee and boil once before serving\n</string>
    <string name="a20">14 oz. chick peas drained and rinsed well.\n
1/4 cocoa powder.\n
4 tsp maple syrup (or 2tsp liquid stevia).\n
2 tsp vanilla extract.\n
1/4 cup almond milk (or other dairy free milk).\n
\nSteps:\n\n
Add everything to a food processor or blender except milk blend well.\n


Slowly add milk until you get the desired texture. Taste and add more syrup/chocolate as needed.\n</string>

    <string name="c1">100 gms mixed vegetables, chopped\n
100 gms eggplant\n
30 gms cottage cheese\n
10 gms cornflour\n
60 ml oil\n
5 gms ginger, chopped\n
5 gms celery, chopped\n
5 gms onion\n
5 gms garlic\n
5 gms red chilli\n
6 gms tomato\n
5 gms oyster sauce\n
5 ml rice wine\n
5 ml vinegar\n
5 gms salt\n
5 gms castor sugar\n
5 gms white pepper\n
5 ml sesame oil\n
10 gms corn flour\n
3 gms sichuan pepper\n
150 ml stock water\n
\nHow to Make Stuffed Eggplant with Schezwan Sauce\n\n
1.Stuff the eggplant with chopped vegetables and cottage cheese mixture.\n
2.Coat it with dry cornflour and deep fry.\n
3.Heat oil in wok. Add garlic, ginger, onion, oyster sauce, rice wine, chilli, vinegar, sichuan Pepper. Tomato ketchup and sauté it well.\n
4.Now add stock and adjust the seasoning and give a touch with corn flour.\n
5.At last add the fried eggplant, toss it well in sauce, sprinkle with spring onion and serve hot.\n</string>
    <string name="c2">250 gms chicken mince\n
1 tbsp garlic, chopped\n
3 tbsp carrots, finely chopped\n
3 tbsp spring onion, finely chopped\n
1 tbsp ginger, finely chopped\n
1 tbsp soya sauce\n
1 tbsp oyster sauce\n
1 tsp sesame oil\n
1 tsp pepper powder\n
1 egg\n
1/2 cup almonds (blanched), chopped\n
Oil (for greasing)\n
\nHow to Make Almond and Chicken Momos (without shell)\n\n
1.Place the chicken mince in a bowl.\n
2.Add all the ingredients except almonds and divide it into equal-sized balls.\n
3.Roll these balls in the blanched and chopped almonds and carefully place these small balls on a greased plate.\n
4.Get the steamer ready and steam these on high heat for 15 minutes.\n
5.Remove and serve the momos hot.\n</string>
    <string name="c3">200 gms boneless skinless chicken thigh (trimmed)\n
to taste salt and pepper\n
100 gms yogurt\n
5 gms chilli powder\n
25 gms ginger garlic paste\n
5 gram coriander leaves\n
Oil to fry\n
50 gms peri peri sauce\n
100 gms potato fries\n
\nHow to Make Peri Peri Chicken Satay\n\n
1.Soak the skewers for at least 60 minutes or more totally submerged in water before using it to prevent burns. You may skip this part if pan grilling.\n
2.Marinate thigh chicken with yogurt, chilli powder, ginger garlic paste, peri peri sauce, salt and pepper.
3.Refrigerate and use when ready. You may make this a day or more ahead of time.\n
4.Place in a zip lock bag, or sealed containers and refrigerate for at least 2 hours, preferably overnight.\n
5.When ready to grill. Using tong remove excess marinates and reserve.\n
6.Pre heat grill to medium- high heat.\n
7.Place chicken over medium heat, and then brush with oil to prevent chicken from sticking. Grill for about 10 to 15 minutes, rotating from sides for even cooking. Keep an eye on it -- if they are browning too quickly, turn the heat down.
8.Grill in batches if you have a small grill. Transfer the skewers to a platter.\n
9.In a small saucepan simmer the remaining peri peri marinade and the one from the chicken for about 7 minutes.\n
10.Serve with chicken, heat oil and prepare the potatoes fries, serve as a bed for chicken.\n</string>
    <string name="c4">Noodles\n
1 tsp Salt\n
1 tsp Oil\n
1 tsp Garlic paste\n
1 tsp Ginger paste\n
1/2 Cup Beans\n
1/2 Cup Cabbage, chopped\n
1/2 Cup Carrot, chopped\n
1/2 Cup Spring onion, chopped\n
1/2 Cup Capsicum, chopped\n
2 Tbsp Soy sauce\n
2 Tbsp Green chilli sauce\n
1 Tbsp Tomato sauce\n
\nHow to Make Veg Hakka Noodles\n\n
1.Boil the noodles in a pan till it starts to simmer.\n
2.Add salt and some oil to the boiling noodles.\n
3.When the noodles start to e a little sticky, drain the excess water and wash them in cold water.\n
4.In another pan, heat about 3 teaspoon of oil.\n
5.Put ginger paste followed by garlic paste. Saute them well till golden brown.\n
6.Now add all the vegetables to the pan.\n
7.Saute them well and add soy sauce, green chilli sauce and tomato sauce.\n
8.Mix them well and now add the boiled noodles to them.\n
9.Mix them thoroughly with the vegetables.\n
10.Serve hot.\n
 </string>
    <string name="c5">2 Tbsp oil\n
2 tsp ginger-garlic paste\n
1/2 cup spring onion, chopped\n
1/2 cup carrot, chopped\n
1/2 cup cabbage, chopped\n
1 capsicum, chopped\n
1 tsp salt\n
1 tbsp soy sauce\n
1 tbsp vinegar\n
1 cup rice\n
\nHow to Make Veg Fried Rice\n\n
1.Heat oil in a pan.\n
2.Add ginger garlic paste to it, saute a little.\n
3.Now add spring onion, carrot, cabbage and capsicum.\n
4.Saute and cook them well together.\n
5.Now add salt along with soy sauce and vinegar.\n
6.Mix thoroughly till simmer and add cooked rice to the pan.\n
7.Combine the mix with rice thoroughly.\n
8.Serve your hot Veg Fried Rice in a bowl, garnished with coriander leaves.\n
    </string>
    <string name="c6">For Frying Potatoes:\n\n
2 Nos Potatoes, sliced\n
5 Tbsp Corn flour\n
1 1/2 Tbsp Salt\n
2 tsp Chilli Powder\n
\nFor Honey Chilli Sauce:\n\n
1 1/2 tsp Garlic\n
1 tsp Ginger\n
2 Nos Whole Red Chillies , chopped\n
1 tsp Chilli Flakes\n
2 tsp Tomato Sauce\n
2 tsp Chilli Sauce\n
1 tsp Vinegar\n
2 Tbsp Honey\n
1 tsp Salt\n
4 tsp Sesame Seeds , roasted\n
2 Bulbs Spring Onions\n
How to Make Honey Chilli Potato\n
\nFor Frying Potatoes:\n\n
1.Take two potatoes and cut them into slices in a bowl.\n
2.In the bowl add corn flour, salt and red chilli powder.\n
3.Toss them well so that the mixture coats the sliced potatoes properly.\n
4.Now heat oil in a broad pan and deep fry the potatoes on medium flame till golden brown and crisp.\n
5.Do not fry on high flame otherwise they will burn from outside and remain uncooked from inside.\n
6.In another pan dry roast the sesame seeds on low heat till light brown and keep aside.\n
\nFor Preparing Honey Chilli Sauce:\n\n
1.Heat oil and add garlic, ginger, whole red chillies, chilli flakes and tomato sauce. Stir well.\n
2.Now add chilli sauce, vinegar, honey and salt. Mix all the ingredients well to make a sauce.\n
3.Add the fried potatoes and coat them well with the sauce.\n
4.Toss well and sprinkle the roasted sesame seeds and spring onions.\n
5.Combine the ingredients well and serve the crunchy honey chilli potatoes immediately.\n

</string>
    <string name="c7">450 Gram Chicken Thigh/Breast (cut crosswise into 1/2-inch-thin strips)\n
1 tsp Sesame Oil (toasted)\n
1/4 tsp White Pepper (finely ground)\n
1 tsp Ginger Juice\n
2 Tbsp Peanut Oil or Vegetable oil (divided)\n
5-6 Garlic cloves (minced)\n
1 Tbsp Ginger, grated\n
1 tsp Red Chilli Flakes\n
1/2 Cup Red Onion , chopped\n
A handful Snow Peas (trimmed)\n
1/2 Red Bell Pepper (cut into thin strips)\n
\nFor the sauce:\n\n
1 Tbsp Rice Vinegar\n
2 Tbsp Soy Sauce\n
2 tsp Dark Soy Sauce\n
2 tsp Chinese Rice Wine\n
1/2 Tbsp Brown Sugar\n
1 tsp Cornflour\n
How to Make Garlic Soya Chicken\n
1.In a large bowl, toss chicken strips with toasted sesame oil and white pepper. Marinate for 10-15 minutes. Keep aside.\n
2.In a small bowl, stir together rice vinegar, soy sauce, dark soy sauce, Chinese rice wine, brown sugar and cornstarch. Set aside.\n
3.Heat a wok or large frying pan over high heat. Add 1 tablespoon of oil. When the oil is hot, add the chicken pieces, spreading it out as much as possible.\n
4.Sear for 1 minute without stirring until the edges are lightly browned, then stir to cook all sides until just cooked through, about 2-3 minutes more. Transfer chicken to a bowl and set aside.\n
5.Reheat the same wok, Put in another tablespoon of oil, add in garlic, ginger, and red chili flakes. Stir-fry over low heat for about 10-15 seconds, or until aromatic, taking care not to burn the garlic.\n
6.Turn up the heat to high, add in snow peas and red onion, and stir-fry for another 30 seconds.\n
7.Add in red bell pepper, and cook for one minute - making sure to stir and toss the ingredients well.\n
8.When the vegetables are bright and almost crisp-tender, stir in the cooked chicken.\n
9.Take the prepared sauce, give it a stir, and quickly pour it into the wok, cooking until the sauce thickens.\n
10.Add in one or two tablespoon of water if needed, toss well, and cook for a further 30 seconds or the mixture is hot and bubbly.\n
11.Turn heat off, and transfer to a serving plate.\n
12.Serve hot with steamed rice.\n</string>
    <string name="c8">1 tsp chilli bean paste\n
300 gms diced silken tofu\n
1/2 tsp sichuan oil\n
2 Tbsp cooking oil\n
1 tsp spicy black bean\n
100 ml water\n
1/2 tsp dark soy\n
1/2 tsp red chili powder\n
1/2 tsp sugar\n
1 tsp spring onions, chopped\n
2 Tbsp leeks sliced\n
2 Tbsp water\n
1 tsp ginger, chopped\n
1 tsp garlic, chopped\n
\nHow to Make Mapo Tofu with Spring Onion and Black Beans\n\n
1.Heat cooking oil and Sichuan oil in wok or pan, put chili bean paste, spicy black bean, sauté it.\n
2.Add ginger, garlic, chili powder and sauté for a while.\n
3.Add dark soy and water.\n
4.Put silken tofu, leeks, spring onion, and add sugar, let it boil for 2 minutes.\n
5.Meanwhile take a stainless steel bowl put potato starch and water to prepare thickening starch.\n
6.Adjust the thickening with potato starch and add it.\n
7.Serve hot\n</string>
    <string name="c9">4 Cups Water\n
1 tsp Ginger, finely chopped\n
1 tsp Garlic, finely chopped\n
1 tsp Green chilies , finely chopped\n
1 Tbsp Coriander leaves - finely chopped, finely chopped\n
2 Tbsp French beans, finely chopped\n
2 Tbsp Carrots, finely chopped\n
2 Tbsp Cabbage , finely chopped\n
2 Tbsp Capsicum , finely chopped\n
2 Tbsp Mushrooms , finely chopped\n
2 Spring onions, finely chopped\n
1 tsp Pepper\n
1 Tbsp Soya sauce\n
4 Tbsp Cornflour - mixed with\n
1 Cup Water\n
2 stems Spring onion\n
as required oil and salt\n
\nHow to Make Vegetable Manchow Soup\n\n
1.In a pan, add some oil and stir fry the ginger, garlic, coriander leaves and green chilies for about two minutes.\n
2.Add all the vegetables, pepper, ajinomoto, salt and continue to stir-fry for two more minutes.\n
3.Add the Soya sauce, water and salt.\n
4.Let it boil, reduce the heat and add the cornflour mixed with water and stir constantly till it thickens slightly.\n
5.Remove from heat and serve immediately.\n
6.Garnish with spring onion stems.\n</string>
    <string name="c10">2 packets Noodles\n
1 TBSP Vegetable oil\n
1 Cup Onion, sliced\n
1 Cup Peppers, sliced\n
1 Cup Carrot, julienne\n
1 Cup Spring onions , sliced\n
1 Cup Mushrooms, sliced\n
1/2 Iceberg/romaine lettuce\n
1 TBSP Ginger and garlic chilli paste\n
1 TBSP Soy sauce\n
1 TBSP Schezwan sauce\n
1/2 TSP Turmeric powder\n
1 TSP Sugar\n
1 TBSP Coriander, chopped\n
1 TBSP Lemon juice\n
1 TSP Vinegar\n
\nHow to Make Quick Noodles\n\n
1.Cook the noodles in boiling water according to the instructions depending upon the kind of noodles you are using. Drain, cool under running water.\n
2.Add a few drops of oil to the noodles to prevent them from sticking to each other.\n
3.In a wok, heat some oil to almost smoking point.\n
4.Then add the sliced onions, peppers, carrots, spring onions and mushrooms and the ginger garlic chilli paste.\n
5.Mix the soy, schezwan, turmeric and the sugar in a small bowl and mix well.\n
6.Add this mix to the vegetables. Then add the noodles and toss well. Season to taste.\n
7.Finish with chopped coriander and toasted crushed peanuts and lemon juice.\n</string>
    <string name="c11">5 pieces bok choy or any green vegetable.\n
1 whole chicken (boiled)\n
3-4 spring onions\n
5 large spoons of chicken stock\n
10 mushrooms\n
\nHow to Make Cantonese Chicken Soup\n\n
1.De-skin the chicken and cut it into 10 -12 big pieces.\n
2.Now, slice the mushrooms into equal halves.\n
3.Layer the chicken pieces, bok choy and the mushrooms in a container.\n
4.Add the chicken stock to this.\n
5.Put this in an oven to cook for an hour and the soup is ready.\n</string>
    <string name="c12">For the tofu:\n\n
100 gms tofu\n
2 tsp chilly paste\n
1 Lemon grass stick\n
2 Shallots , chopped\n
1 inch ginger , chopped\n
2 tsp soya sauce\n
3 Garlic cloves, chopped\n
1 inch red onion , chopped\n
2 tsp honey\n
Handful of coriander leaves, chopped\n
1 tsp refined oil\n
\nFor the fried rice:\n\n
Carrots, chopped\n
Spring onions, chopped\n
To flavor salt and pepper\n
1 Fresh red chilly, chopped\n
1 Ginger, chopped\n
2 tsp soya sauce\n
1/2 Lemon (squeezed)\n
Handful Handful of coriander , chopped\n
1 tsp olive oil\n
\nHow to Make Stir Fried Tofu with Rice\n\n
1.Drizzle refined oil in a preheated pan and add chopped mariner and stir well.\n
2.Then add ginger, garlic, shallots and salt and pepper.\n
3.Add red chilly paste, soya sauce and honey.\n
4.Add some coriander leaves and mix it all together.\n
For the fried rice:
1.Drizzle olive oil in a pre-heated pan and add carrots, spring onions, ginger and salt and pepper.\n
2.Then add fresh red chilly, lemon juice and soya sauce and stir all together.\n
3.Add some chopped coriander leaves.\n
4.Cook it away for 5-7 minutes.\n
5.Serve it on a platter.\n
</string>
    <string name="c13">250 Gram Chicken mince\n
2 Eggs (slightly beaten)\n
3/4 Cup Refined flour\n
1/2 tsp Garlic paste\n
1/2 tsp Ginger paste\n
For deep frying Oil\n
2 Tbsp Oil\n
1 tsp Garlic, finely chopped\n
1/2 Cup Onions, finely chopped\n
1 Large Capsicum, finely chopped\n
\nFor sauce, mix together:\n\n
3 Tbsp Corn flour (blended)\n
1/2 Cup Water\n\n
2 Tbsp Vinegar\n
2 tsp Salt\n
2 tsp Soya sauce\n
1/2 Cup Tomato puree\n
2 Tbsp Celery, chopped\n
2 Cups Water\n
\nHow to Make Chicken Manchurian\n\n
1.Mix together the chicken, egg, flour, garlic and ginger paste, enough water so as to have a thick batter. Leave this for 5-10 minutes.\n
2.Heat the oil, keeping the heat high drop heaped teaspoonfuls of batter and fry to a golden brown. Drain on absorbent paper till required.\n
3.Heat 2 Tbsp of oil, and stir-fry the garlic and onion in it over high heat, till the onions look glossy. Add the capsicum and turn around a few times.\n
4.Add the sauce mixture, and simmer till the sauce thickens and becomes translucent.\n
5.Add the fried balls, turn around a few times and serve.\n</string>
    <string name="c14">250 Gram Fish pieces (Boneless)\n
1/2 Cup Maida\n
1/2 Cup Corn flour\n
1 tsp Baking powder\n
2 tsp Soy sauce\n
2 Tbsp Celery, finely chopped\n
1 tsp Pepper\n
Salt\n
Oil\n
To garnish Spring onions\n
\nFor the sauce:\n\n
1 Tbsp Ginger, chopped\n
1 Tbsp Garlic, chopped\n
1 Tbsp Green chilly, chopped\n
4 Tbsp Soy sauce\n
5 Tbsp Tomato sauce\n
1 Tbsp Chilli sauce\n
1 Tbsp Corn flour\n
\nHow to Make Chilli Fish\n\n
1.Cut the fish into finger pieces.\n
2.Make a batter with corn flour, maida, baking powder, soy sauce, celery, pepper powder, water and salt.\n
3.Dip the fish pieces in the batter and fry in oil till golden brown. Transfer fish into a serving plate.\n
\nPrepare the sauce:\n\n
1.Heat oil in a pan.\n
2.Saute garlic, ginger and green chilly. Add soy sauce, chilly and tomato sauce to it.\n
3.Finally add corn flour mixed with water to it and stir well. Once it starts to boil, remove form fire.\n
4.At the time of serving, pour the sauce on top of fried fish pieces and mix well.\n
5.Garnish with chopped spring onions.\n</string>
    <string name="c15">For the potatoes:\n
2 potatoes (sliced), peeled\n
3-4 tbsp cornflour or maida\n
to taste salt\n
1 tsp red chilli powder\n
oil (for deep frying)\n
\nFor the base:\n\n
1 tsp oil\n
spring onions (with stalk), fried\n
1 tbsp garlic paste\n
1 capsicum, sliced\n
2 tbsp honey\n
to taste salt\n
1/4 tsp soya sauce\n
3 tsp white sesame seeds\n
2 tsp chilli sauce\n
How to Make Honey Chilli Potatoes\n
\nPrpeare the potatoes:\n\n
1.In a bowl, add cornflour or maida, salt and red chilli powder.\n
2.Add the sliced potatoes and mix well until the potatoes are coated.\n
3.Heat oil in a wok and deep fry the potatoes until golden. Keep aside.\n
\nPrepare the base:\n\n
1.In a wok, add oil, garlic paste and spring onions. Saute on high heat for 1 minute.\n
2.Add capsicum, honey, salt, soya sauce, chilli sauce. Saute for 2-3 minutes.\n
3.Add the deep-fried potatoes and sesame seeds. Mix well and serve hot.</string>
    <string name="c16">2 Tbsp oil\n
1 Egg\n
1 tsp ginger, chopped\n
6-7 Garlic cloves (mashed)\n
1 red chilli, chopped\n
2 cups rice, steamed\n
1 tsp salt\n
1 tsp black pepper powder\n
1 tsp soya sauce\n
1 tsp coriander, chopped\n
2 tsp spring onion, chopped\n
\nHow to Make Garlic and Egg Fried Rice\n\n
1.Heat oil in a pan on medium flame and add the chopped garlic to it. Cook until light golden.\n
2.Now add a teaspoon of spring onion, ginger and red chilli. Saute for a minute.\n
3.Break an egg in the pan. Mix and cook until scrambled.\n
4.Then pour the steamed rice and combine well with the ingredients with light hands.\n
5.Add salt and black pepper powder and mix thoroughly pouring soya sauce over the rice.\n
6.Again add a teaspoon of spring onion to the rice and stir fry for a minute.\n
7.Transfer the hot and delicious fried rice in a bowl and serve hot garnished with spring onions and some coriander leaves.\n

</string>
    <string name="c17">5 Gram Carrot\n
5 GRAM Cabbage\n
5 GRAM Black mushrooms\n
5 GRAM Button mushrooms\n
5 GRAM Bamboo shoots\n
5 GRAM Bean sprouts\n
5 GRAM Fresh beans\n
100 GRAM Chicken\n
60 GRAM 60 gm prawns\n
1 Tbsp soya sauce\n
1/2 Tbsp chili powder\n
1/2 tsp white pepper\n
2 Tbsp corn flour\n
1 egg\n
1 Tbsp coriander\n
1 tsp chili oil\n
2 cups stock\n
1 1/2 Tbsp vinegar\n
Salt to taste\n
\nHow to Make Hot and Sour Soup\n\n
1.Cut all vegetables, chicken and prawns in julienne style.\n
2.Take a wok and add the stock and add all vegetables along with chicken and cook.\n
3.Later add pepper, soy, salt, coriander, chili oil and vinegar.\n
4.Add corn flour for thickness and lastly the egg\n</string>
    <string name="c18">100 Gram Soya nuggets (soaked in water for 1/2 an hour and drained\n
2 Tbsp Salt\n
1/2 Tbsp Garlic paste\n
2 Tbsp Oil\n
1 Cup Spring onions, finely chopped\n
2 Tbsp Green chillies, sliced\n
2 Tbsp Soya sauce\n
2 Tbsp Vinegar\n
\nFor garnishing Some greens\n\n
How to Make Chilli Soya Nuggets\n\n
1.Mix together the nuggets, 1 teaspoon salt and garlic paste.\n
2.Heat the oil, add the onions and stir-fry over high heat till a little brown at the edges.\n
3.Add the green chillies and stir a few times, add the remaindered salt, soya sauce, vinegar and the nuggets.\n
4.Stir-fry over high heat for a minute or so and serve garnished with some greens.\n</string>
    <string name="c19">1/2 Tbsp chilli paste\n
1/2 Tbsp shrimp paste\n
1/2 Tbsp roasted peanut powder\n
1/2 Tbsp tamarind water\n
2 tsp chopped ginger flower\n
1/2 tsp chopped whole lime\n
A squeeze of lemon\n
1/4 cup diced pineapple\n
1/4 cup diced cucumber\n
1/4 cup diced turnip\n
1/4 cup diced raw mango\n
1/4 cup beans sprouts\n
1/4 cup cooked jelly fish\n
1/4 cup diced tofu\n
1/4 cup fried wheat dough\n
2 lettuce leaves\n
Parsley\n
\nHow to Make Chinese Salad\n\n
1.Mix all the ingredients well.\n
2.Toss the salad on lettuce leaves.\n
3.Garnish with parsley.\n
4.Serve topped with roasted peanuts.\n</string>
    <string name="c20">To pan sear the chicken Oil\n
\nFor the marinade:\n\n
2 Chicken breast\n
2 Tbsp Char siu sauce\n
1 Tbsp Garlic and ginger\n
1 tsp Rice vinegar\n
1 tsp Honey\n
1 tsp Red chilli paste (optional)\n
1/2 tsp Sesame oil\n
To taste Salt and pepper\n
\nHow to Make Asian BBQ Chicken\n\n
1.In a bowl, mix all the marinade ingredients. Mix the chicken with the marinade and keep aside for 15 minutes.\n
2.Pan sear the chicken from both sides.\n
3.Serve with garlic and egg fried rice.\n</string>


    <string name="t1">For the gozleme dough\n\n
7g sachet fast-action dried yeast\n
1 tsp golden caster sugar\n
250g plain flour\n
2 tbsp olive oil\n

\nFor the filling\n\n
1 tbsp olive oil, plus extra to finish\n
500g pack lamb mince\n
2 garlic cloves, crushed\n
2 tsp ground cumin\n
2 tsp ground coriander\n
1 tsp ground cinnamon\n
1 tsp mild chilli powder\n
50g raisin\n
zest 1 lemon\n

3 spring onions, finely sliced\n
50g toasted pine nut\n
100g feta cheese\n
For the sauce\n
8 tbsp tomato ketchup\n
2 tbsp pomegranate molasses\n
1 tbsp very finely chopped red onion\n
\n Method\n\n
For the dough, mix the yeast, sugar and 175ml lukewarm water in a small bowl. Stir to dissolve the yeast, then set aside for 10 mins, or until the liquid starts to froth.\n

Mix the flour with ½ tsp salt in a big bowl. Make a well in the centre, pour in the yeasty mixture and olive oil, and mix to a dough. Knead for 10 mins, then put the dough in a lightly oiled bowl and cover with oiled cling film. Leave somewhere quite warm until doubled in size.\n

Meanwhile, make the filling. Heat the oil in a frying pan, add the mince and fry, breaking up lumps as you go, until well browned. Stir in the garlic, spices and raisins, and fry for a few more mins, then turn off the heat and stir in the lemon zest, spring onions, pine nuts and seasoning.\n Set aside to cool a little.\n

Divide the dough into 4. Working a piece at a time, roll out on a lightly floured surface to 25 x 30cm, without the dough splitting. With a long edge of the pastry laying in front of you, spoon ¼ of the mince on the bottom half – leaving a 2cm border all round. Crumble over ¼ of the feta.\n Fold the other half of the dough over the filling, folding in and pinching the edges to seal in the lamb. Repeat with the remaining ingredients.\n

Heat a large frying pan over a high heat and brush the gozleme all over with oil.\n

Cook in batches for 3-5 mins on each side, or until golden and heated through. Quickly mix the tomato ketchup, pomegranate and onion, and serve with the hot, crispy gozleme.\n


    </string>
    <string name="t2">2 Medium aubergines\n

juice 1 lemon\n

2-3 garlic cloves, crushed\n
150ml pot thick yogurt\n

small bunch dill, leaves chopped\n

    Ingredients
2 medium aubergines

juice 1 lemon

2-3 garlic cloves, crushed
150ml pot thick yogurt

small bunch dill, leaves chopped
\nMethod\n\n
Heat grill to very hot. Slice the aubergines in half lengthways, then grill for 25 mins, turning occasionally, until soft \n The skin will remain firm, but the flesh will soften. Lift the aubergines off the grill and leave until cool enough to handle.\n

Using a sharp knife, score the grilled flesh and scoop out the flesh with a spoon. Tip into a bowl and mash with a fork until you get a thick pulp. Beat in the lemon juice and garlic.\n Add the yogurt and dill, and season. Serve while still warm.\n
    </string>
    <string name="t3">1 leg of lamb\n

zest and juice 1 lemon and 1 orange\n
4 tbsp olive oil\n

2 tbsp clear honey\n
1 tbsp each of cinnamon\n

, fennel seeds, ground cumin\n
3 garlic cloves, crushed\n
\nMethod\n\n

Put the lamb into a large food bag with all the juice and marinate overnight.\n

The next day, take the lamb out of the fridge 1 hr before you want to cook it. Heat oven to 220C/200C fan/gas 7.\n Take the lamb out of the marinade (reserve remaining marinade) and pat dry.\n Rub with half the oil and roast for 15-20 mins until browned. Remove lamb and reduce oven to 160C/140C fan/gas 3.

Mix the zests, remaining oil, honey, spices and garlic with plenty of seasoning. Lay a large sheet of baking parchment on a large sheet of foil.\n Sit the lamb leg on top, rub all over with the paste and pull up the sides of the foil.\n Drizzle marinade into base, and scrunch foil to seal.

Roast for 4 hrs, until very tender. Rest, still wrapped, for 30 mins.\n Unwrap and serve with juices.\n
    </string>
    <string name="t4">135g pack raspberry jelly\n
500ml double cream\n
1 tsp rosewater\n
12 raspberries, halved\n
Dizzle of clear honey\n

Small handful mint leaves\n
1 tbsp pistachio, chopped\n
    \nMethod\n\n
Boil a kettle. Break the jelly cubes into a jug, pour over 100ml boiling water and stir to dissolve.\n Gently warm the cream in a small pan, then remove from the heat and pour in the jelly mixture.\n Stir in the rose water, then tip the mixture back into your jug. Divide the jelly between 6 small glasses and chill for 2 hrs or until set.\n Can be made 1 day ahead.\n

Remove the jellies from the fridge about 20 mins before serving.\n Divide the raspberries between them, then add a drizzle of honey, a few mint leaves and a sprinkling of pistachios to each.\n</string>
    <string name="t5">Small handful pine nuts or flaked almonds\n
1 tbsp olive oil\n

1 large onion

, halved and sliced\n
2 cinnamon sticks, broken in half\n
500g lean lamb neck fillet, cubed\n
250g basmati rice\n
1 lamb or vegetable stock cube\n
12 ready-to-eat dried apricots\n

Handful fresh mint leaves, roughly chopped\n
\nMethod\n\n
Dry-fry the pine nuts or almonds in a large pan until lightly toasted, then tip onto a plate.\n Add the oil to the pan, then fry the onion and cinnamon together until starting to turn golden. Turn up the heat, stir in the lamb, fry until the meat changes colour, then tip in the rice and cook for 1 min, stirring all the time.

Pour in 500ml boiling water, crumble in the stock cube, add the apricots, then season to taste.\n Turn the heat down, cover and simmer for 12 mins until the rice is tender and the stock has been absorbed.\n Toss in the pine nuts and mint and serve.</string>
    <string name="t6">6 boneless, skinless chicken thighs (about 500g/1lb 2oz)\n
2 tbsp olive oil\n

1 tsp fennel seed

, crushed\n
1 tsp ground cumin\n
1 tsp sweet smoked paprika

 (pimenton)\n
1 garlic clove, crushed\n
1 tsp red wine vinegar smoky aïoli, to serve (see tips below)\n
\nMethod\n\n
You need 15 skewers: if wooden, soak in water for 10 mins. \nCut chicken into 3cm pieces and place in a bowl. \n
Add 1 tbsp olive oil, the spices, garlic and vinegar, toss well and season. You can do this up to a day before and refrigerate.\n

Thread 2-3 pieces on each skewer. Pour remaining oil in a frying pan or rub onto a griddle pan.\n Get the pan hot and sear the chicken for 3-4 mins on each side – you may have to do this in batches, keeping the cooked skewers warm in a low oven.\n Serve with smoky aïoli if you like.\n</string>
    <string name="t7">2 tbsp sunflower or vegetable oil\n
1 small onion, finely chopped\n
1 garlic clove, crushed\n
400g can chickpea, washed and drained\n
1 tsp ground cumin\n

1 tsp ground coriander (or use more cumin)\n
handful parsley, chopped, or 1 tsp dried mixed herbs\n
1 egg, beaten\n
\nMethod\n\n
Heat 1 tbsp oil in a large pan, then fry the onion and garlic over a low heat for 5 mins until softened.\n Tip into a large mixing bowl with the chickpeas and spices, then mash together with a fork or potato masher until the chickpeas are totally broken down.\n Stir in the parsley or dried herbs, with seasoning to taste.\n Add the egg, then squish the mixture together with your hands.\n

Mould the mix into 6 balls, then flatten into patties.\n Heat the remaining oil in the pan, then fry the falafels on a medium heat for 3 mins on each side, until golden brown and firm.\n Serve hot or cold with couscous, pitta bread or salad.\n</string>
    <string name="t8">200g whole blanched almond, toasted and roughly chopped\n
85g icing sugar, plus extra to serve\n
85g butter, melted\n
2 tsp orange flower water\n
1 tsp cinnamon\n

1 egg yolk\n
190g pack brik pastry
clear honey, to serve\n
\nFor the cream\n\n
zest 1 orange\n

300g Greek yogurt\n
300ml tub double cream\n
2 tbsp icing sugar, sifted\n
\nMethod\n\n
Set aside a quarter of the almonds.\n
Put the rest in a food processor with the icing sugar, half the butter, orange blossom water, cinnamon and egg yolk.\n
Whizz to a paste. Scrape into a bowl and stir in most of the remaining chopped nuts.\n

Unroll one sheet of brik pastry at a time, brush all over with melted butter and halve into 2 semi-circles.\n Shape 1 heaped tbsp of the nut mixture to look like a thin wedge shape along half the pastry edge you’ve just cut (leaving 2.5cm border on the rounded side), so it looks as if you’re cutting the semi-circle of pastry into pieces like a cake.\n
Roll up like a pastry cone, sealing the nut mixture inside, then brush all over with more butter and fold over the open, wide end to seal.\n Sit on a baking tray, end flap side down to help it stay closed, and repeat until nut mixture is used up.\n Cover with cling film and chill.\n
Put zest, yogurt, cream and icing sugar in a mixing bowl. Cover and chill.\n

Heat oven to 200C/180C fan/gas 6, put the pastries in and bake for 15 mins until golden and crisp.\n Just before they’re ready, beat together the yogurt mixture until thick. Pile pastries onto a serving dish, drizzle with honey and scatter with remaining nuts.\n
Serve with the orange cream and Honeyed orange and grapefruit.\n</string>
    <string name="t9">400g lamb

 mince\n
1 garlic clove, crushed\n
1 tsp ground cumin\n
2 tsp ground coriander\n
2 handfuls mint leaves, half chopped\n
2 large tomatoes, deseeded and diced\n
4 small khobez flatbreads or 4 soft flour tortillas (you can buy khobez flatbreads from larger Sainsbury)\n
4 tbsp low-fat natural yogurt\n

\nMethod\n\n
Cook the lamb mince for 5-6 mins in a non-stick frying pan over a high heat.\n
When starting to brown, stir in the garlic and spices, then cook for 2-3 mins more until the mince is brown and there is no liquid left in the pan.\n Stir in the chopped mint, tomatoes and some seasoning.\n

Heat the grill to high. Arrange the flatbreads on a baking tray and spread the mince mixture over them. Grill for 2-3 mins.\n To serve, scatter over the whole mint leaves and drizzle with yogurt.\n</string>

    <string name="t10">1 x 400g can chickpea, dont drain\n
1 tbsp tahini paste\n
1 fat garlic clove, chopped\n
3 tbsp 0% fat Greek yogurt good squeeze lemon juice\n
\nMethod\n\n
Drain the chickpeas into a sieve set over a bowl or jug to catch the liquid. \nTip the chickpeas, tahini, garlic and yogurt into a food processor or blender and whizz to smooth.\n

Whizz in a tbsp of the chickpea liquid at a time until you have a nice consistency, then scrape into a bowl.\n

Stir in a squeeze of lemon juice and season to taste.\n</string>
    <string name="t11">4 lamb leg steaks\n
2 tsp seasoning (we used Schwartz Lamb Simply Shake seasoning).\n
1 tsp dried oregan, or mixed herbs would do Small bunch mint, leaves only, chopped.\n
2 x 150g tubs low-fat plain yogurt.\n
4 pitta breads, white or wholemeal.\n
½ iceberg lettuce, shredded\n
1 red onion, thinly sliced\n
1 lemon, cut into wedges for squeezing, optional.\n
\nMethod\n\n
Heat grill to high. Season the lamb, then grill for 2 mins on each side until browned, but still very rare.\n Meanwhile, mix the seasoning, oregano and half of the mint into one of the tubs of yogurt, smother this over the lamb, then return to the grill for another 2-3 mins or until the yogurt is blistered and the meat is cooked to your liking.\n

Leave the meat to rest on a board for a few mins while you toast the pittas, shred the lettuce and thinly slice the red onion.\n Stir the rest of the mint into the second tub of yogurt.\n Thickly slice the meat and stuff into the pitta bread with the salad and minted yogurt.\n Squeeze over lemon juice before tucking in, if you like.

 </string>
    <string name="t12">225g self-raising flour\n
½ tsp ground cinnamon\n
175g softened butter\n
100g light muscovado sugar\n
3 tbsp clear honey\n
2 eggs, beaten\n
2 medium, ripe bananas , about 250g/9oz total weight in their skins\n
100g stoned dates\n

50g pack walnut pieces\n
\nMethod\n\n
Preheat the oven to 160C/Gas 3/fan oven 140C.\n Line the base and long sides of a 900g/2lb loaf tin with greaseproof paper, buttering the tin and paper.\n

Tip the flour, cinnamon, butter, sugar, 2 tablespoons of the honey and the eggs into a large mixing bowl.\n Mash the bananas and chop the dates (kitchen scissors are easiest for this) and add to the bowl.\n Beat the mixture for 2-3 minutes, using a wooden spoon or hand-held mixer, until well blended.\n

Spoon into the prepared tin and level the top. Scatter the walnut pieces over.\n Bake for 1 hour, then lightly press the top – it will feel firm if cooked. If not, bake for a further 10 minutes.\n

Cool for 15 minutes, then lift out of the tin using the paper.\n When cold, drizzle the remaining honey over. Cut into thick slices.\n</string>
    <string name="t13">2 red onions\n
1 tsp cinnamon\n

1 tbsp olive oil\n

400g lean lamb steak\n
140g wild and basmati rice\n
Handful mint, chopped\n
Handful parsley, chopped\n
120g pack fresh pomegranate seeds\n
50g chopped pistachio\n
50g dried cranberries\n

juice ½ orange\n

juice ½ lemon\n

\nMethod\n\n
Grate 1 onion into a shallow dish, add the cinnamon and ½ tbsp olive oil, then mix.\n Place the lamb steaks in the dish, rub in the marinade, then cover and set aside while you make the rice.\n

Place the rice and 600ml water in a pan. Bring to the boil, then turn down and simmer, covered, until all the water has evaporated – about 20 mins. Take off the lid and cool.\n Finely chop the remaining red onion and mix into the rice along with the herbs, pomegranate, pistachios and cranberries.\n Finally mix in the orange and lemon juice, the remaining olive oil and season well.\n

Remove the lamb from the marinade, shaking off any excess.\n Griddle for about 5 mins on each side, depending on how you like your meat, and serve with a big spoonful of rice.\n</string>
    <string name="t14">1l bottle vodka\n

1 tsp rosewater\n
1 tsp caster sugar\n
100g Turkish delight, chopped, plus a little extra for packaging\n
\nMethod\n\n
Pour 100ml out of the vodka bottle – you can keep this in the freezer for Christmas cocktails.\n Mix the rose water and caster sugar together until the sugar dissolves, then pour into the vodka bottle using a funnel.\n

Wash any sugar off the Turkish delight, then put it in the bottle.\n Screw on the lid and leave to stand for up to a month, swirling occasionally until the Turkish delight dissolves. Serve with soda water and ice, or drizzle neat over vanilla ice cream for a boozy treat.\n</string>
    <string name="t15">100g mascarpone\n
50g Greek yogurt\n
25g icing sugar, sifted\n
2 tbsp orange flower water\n
1 meringue nest, broken into rough pieces\n
3 apricots, stoned and chopped\n
2 cubes Turkish delight, orange flavoured if available, chopped\n
25g skin-on almonds, roughly chopped\n
4 mint leaves, shredded, plus extra to decorate (optional)\n
\n\nMethod\n\n
Place the mascarpone, yogurt, sugar and orange flower water into a large bowl and whisk until thickened.\n Fold the remaining ingredients through, then divide the mix between 2 dessert glasses or bowls and decorate with extra mint, if you like.\n</string>
    <string name="t16">2 aubergines, thickly sliced lengthways\n
2 tbsp vegetable oil, plus extra for brushing\n
3 slices brown or white bread, crusts removed\n
300g tub hummus\n

100g walnuts, toasted\n
Half an 80g pack flat-leaf parsley, leaves roughly chopped\n
200g pack cherry tomatoes, quartered\n
Juice ½ lemon\n

Splash extra-virgin olive oil\n
\nMethod\n\n
Lay the aubergine out in one layer on a large baking sheet.\n Brush sparingly with vegetable oil, then season generously.\n Grill for 15 mins, turning twice and brushing with oil until the slices are softened and cooked through. Meanwhile, whizz the bread into crumbs.\n Add 2 tsp oil and whizz briefly again, to coat.\n

Spread a couple of tsps of hummus on top of each slice of aubergine.\n Tip the breadcrumbs onto a large plate, then press the hummus side of the aubergines into the crumbs to coat.\n Grill again, crumb-side up, for about 3 mins until golden.\n

Toss the walnuts, parsley and cherry tomatoes in a bowl, season, then add the lemon juice and olive oil and toss again.\n Serve the grills with the salad, a dollop more hummus and some pitta bread.\n</string>
    <string name="t17">2 cubes Turkish delight, optional\n
500g pot good-quality vanilla custard\n
½ a 350g/12oz bought madeira loaf\n
300g pack raspberry\n

juice 1 orange\n

200ml tub crème fraîche (use reduced-fat if you like) handful pistachios, roughly chopped\n
\nMethod\n\n
If you don’t want to add the Turkish delight, move on to step 2.\n Snip the Turkish delight into pieces with kitchen scissors into a large bowl and add a few tablespoons of water.\n Microwave on High for 1 min, stirring after 30 secs, or until dissolved and smooth. Tip in the custard and stir together.\n

Break the cake into rough chunks and divide between 6 sundae dishes or serving glasses.\n Mix half of the raspberries with the orange juice in a bowl and crush gently with a fork to break the fruit up slightly.\n Spoon over the cake layer. Cover with the custard, then leave to cool in the fridge for at least 30 mins. Can be made up to 1 day ahead.\n To serve, top the trifles with a dollop of crème fraîche, the remaining raspberries and a sprinkling of pistachios.\n</string>
    <string name="t18">2 aubergines

, thinly sliced lengthways\n
3 tbsp extra-virgin olive oil\n
12 cherry tomatoes, halved\n
1 Middle Eastern flatbread or pitta\n
3 tbsp balsamic vinegar\n

Handful mintbleaves\n
2 shallots, 1 finely chopped, the other thinly sliced\n
1 red chilli, finely chopped\n
50g goat cheese, crumbled\n
Handful wild rocket, to serve.\n
\nMethod\n\n
Heat oven to 200C/180C fan/gas 6. Brush the aubergine slices with 1 tbsp of the oil, then season.\n Arrange on a baking tray or sheet and roast for 20 mins until browned, popping the tomatoes on the tray for the final 5 mins.\n Tear the flatbread into pieces and place on a separate baking sheet. Brown in the oven for 8 mins, or until crisp, then remove.\n

For the dressing, in a small bowl, mix the vinegar, mint, chopped shallots, chilli, remaining oil and some salt and pepper.\n

Scatter the aubergine slices, tomatoes, sliced shallot and crisp flatbread into a serving bowl.\n Pour over the dressing, sprinkle with the goat’s cheese and scatter over a little rocket.\n</string>
    <string name="t19">1.2kg sweet potato, peeled and cut into biggish chunks\n
1 tbsp olive oil\n

\nFor the dressing\n\n
2 shallots (or half a small red onion), finely chopped\n
4 spring onions, finely sliced\n
small bunch chives, snipped into quarters or use mini ones\n
5 tbsp sherry vinegar\n
2 tbsp extra-virgin olive oil\n
2 tbsp honey\n

\nMethod\n\n
Heat oven to 200C/180C fan/gas 6. Toss the sweet potato chunks with the olive oil and some seasoning, and spread on a baking parchment-lined baking sheet.\n Roast for 30 - 35 mins until tender and golden. Cool at room temperature.\n

When just about cool whisk together all the dressing ingredients with a little more seasoning and gently toss through the potato chunks – use your hands to avoid breaking them up.\n</string>
    <string name="t20">2 tbsp olive oil\n

2 red onions, very finely chopped\n
4 garlic cloves, crushed\n
2 tsp each ground cumin and coriander (or 4 tsp Moroccan spice blend)\n
400g can chopped tomatoes\n

½ tsp sugar\n

½ 20g pack mint, finely chopped\n
500g pack lean lamb mince\n
8 dried apricots, finely chopped\n
50g fresh breadcrumbs
pitta bread and salad, to serve\n
\nMethod\n\n
Heat 2 tsp oil in a pan and soften the onions for 5 mins. Add the garlic and spices and cook for a few mins more.\n Spoon half the onion mixture into a bowl and set aside to cool. Add the tomatoes, sugar and seasoning to the remaining onions in the pan and simmer for about 10 mins until reduced.\n

Meanwhile, add the mint, lamb, apricots and breadcrumbs to the cooled onions, season and mix well with your hands. Shape into little meatballs.\n

Heat the rest of the oil in a non-stick pan and fry the meatballs until golden (in batches if you need to). \nStir in the sauce with a splash of water and gently cook everything for a few mins until the meatballs are cooked through.\n Serve with pitta bread and salad.\n</string>


    <string name="o1">
Ingredients Of Carrot Cake\n
100 gms carrot\n
68 gms flour\n
68 gms castor sugar\n
1 Egg\n
68 gms oil\n
2 gms baking soda\n
2 gms baking powder\n
2 gms salt\n
48 gms walnut\n
2 gms cinnamon\n
\nHow to Make Carrot Cake\n\n
1.Grate carrot and squeeze out the excess water.\n
2.Take egg, oil and sugar to mix together.\n
3.In a large mixing bowl take all dry ingredients.\n
4.Mix dry ingredients with wet ingredients.\n
5.Pour the mix into a lined mould and bake at 180 C for 25-30 minutes.\n
6.Decorate with Easter theme garnish.\n</string>
    <string name="o2">
12 chicken wings (separated at the joint)\n
1 tbsp vegetable oil\n
Salt and pepper\n
1/4 cup barbecue sauce\n
1/4 cup hung yogurt\n
1 tsp asian chilli paste\n
1/4 cup honey\n
1 garlic clove, finely chopped\n
1/4 cup sesame seeds\n
\nHow to Make Dragon Fire Wings\n\n
1.Clean and rinse the chicken wings, marinate with hung yogurt and spices with salt and pepper and keep aside.\n
2.Preheat the oven at 450 degree Fahrenheit and roast the wings for 10-12 minutes. In separate pan heat oil, add garlic and let it get brown.\n Add chilli paste, honey and barbeque sauce, Season it and add the cooked chicken wings from oven. Cook it properly till the sauces form a thick consistency and get dressed in chicken wings.
3.Finish with roasted sesame seed and serve.\n</string>
    <string name="o3">
100 gms millet flour\n
100 gms tapioca flour\n
100 gms soy milk\n
5 gms garlic powder\n
5 gms baking powder\n
to taste salt\n
75 gms tomato sauce\n
35 gms mozzarella cheese\n
10 gms prosciutto\n
10 gms pepperoni\n
10 gms chicken salami\n
10 gms salami milano\n
2 gms rosemary\n
20 ml olive oil\n
\nHow to Make Meat Lovers Pizza\n\n
1.Make pizza dough with millet flour, tapioca flour, garlic powder, soy milk, baking powder, water and season it with salt.\n
2.Once the dough is rested for 20 minutes make in to small balls and roll the pizza into thin layer.\n
3.Dock the pizza and cut the edges to make it round.\n
4.Slightly bake the pizza in the oven for 2 minutes.\n
5.Once taken out spread tomato sauce and mozzarella cheese and then bake it in the oven.\n
6.Once 75% done add the pepperoni, chicken salami, salami milano (dry cured and made with pork, sea salt, and red wine) and bake the pizza.\n
7.Once the pizza is fully cooked take it out and cut it into 8 slices.\n
8.Arrange the prosciutto slice on each pizza and garnish with chopped rosemary.\n
9.Serve hot and brush the sides with olive oil.\n</string>
    <string name="o4">
1 almonds\n
2 eggs\n
1/3 granulated sugar\n
2 bittersweet chocolate\n
2 unsalted butter\n
1/2 flour\n
1 baking powder\n
To roll castor sugar\n
To roll icing sugar\n
\nHow to Make Chocolate Nero Cookies\n\n
1.Toast the almonds in the oven until light golden brown and once cool, grind finely and set aside.\n
2.Set a stainless steel bowl over a double boiler, and melt the chocolate and butter together, stirring frequently.\n
3.Once completely melted, remove from the heat.\n
4.In a separate bowl, combine the eggs and sugar.\n
5.Beat on medium speed about 5 minutes, or until the mixture is pale and frothy.\n
6.Slowly pour the chocolate mixture into the eggs mixing well to blend.\n
7.Add the flour, baking powder and almonds to the chocolate and eggs and mix just until smooth dough is created.\n
8.Refrigerate the dough for two hours.\n
9.Heat the oven to 325 degrees F.\n
10.Remove the dough from the refrigerator and take small pieces about the size of large olives and roll into a ball.\n
11.Roll each ball first into the granulated sugar, then into the powdered sugar and place on a parchment covered baking sheet.\n
12.Continue to use up all of the dough in the same manner.\n
13.Bake the cookies for about 15 minutes or until they expand and begin to crack.\n
14.Serve with tea or coffee.\n</string>
    <string name="o5">
100 gms maida\n
500 gms sugar\n
600 gms butter\n
30 gms skim milk powder\n
25 gms custard powder\n
100 gms milk\n
200 gms butter scotch chips (srushed)\n
\nHow to Make Butter Scotch Cookies\n\n
1.Prepare a creaming method cookie dough with all the ingredients, reserving part of the butterscotch chips for garnish.\n
2.Sheet the dough, sprinkle the reserved butterscotch and cut into desired shapes.\n
3.Bake at 175°c for 18-20 minutes.\n</string>
    <string name="o6">
1/4 Cup Ghee or white butter\n
1 1/4 Khaand (A sweetening agent and a healthier substitute of sugar)\n
1 1/2 Ragi flour\n
3/4 Cup Whole wheat flour\n
2 Tbsp Corn starch\n
1/2 tsp Salt\n
1 1/2 tsp Cardamom (ground)\n
2 tsp Baking powder\n
1/2 tsp Baking soda\n
1 Cup Buttermilk\n
1/2 Cup Water\n
1 Cup Dates\n
1 Cup Pistachio\n
\nHow to Make Date And Pistachio Muffin\n\n
1.Pre-heat the oven to 180 degrees Celsius.\n
2.Take your muffin tray and grease it with butter.\n
3.Mix the butter and khaand in a bowl, which will give a cream-like texture.\n
4.Add ragi flour, whole wheat flour, corn starch, ground cardamom, baking powder and baking soda to the mixture.\n
5.Now, add the buttermilk and water to the batter and mix it well until all the ingredients are blended properly.\n
6.Add chopped dates and pistachios to the batter.\n
7.Spoon them into the muffin tray and bake for 25-30 minutes.\n
8.Serve.\n</string>
    <string name="o7">
1 Cup Yellow cornmeal\n
1 tsp Sugar\n
1/2 tsp Baking soda\n
1/2 tsp Salt\n
1 Cup Buttermilk (well-shaken)\n
1 Egg\n
1/4 pound Cheddar (extra sharp), grated\n
1/4 Cup Scallion (white and pale green parts only), finely chopped\n
1-2 Tbsp Pickled jalapenos (drained), finely chopped\n
1/4 Cup Unsalted butter, melted\n
\nSpecial equipment:\n\n
2 Well-seasoned cast-iron corn-stick pans\n
(Each with 7 (5- by 1 1/2-inch) molds*, or a well-seasoned 9-inch cast-iron skillet)\n
\nHow to Make Jalapeno Cheese Fingers\n\n
1.Put oven rack in middle position and preheat oven to 218°C. Heat corn-stick pans in oven 10 minutes.\n
2.Whisk together cornmeal, sugar, baking soda, and salt in a large bowl.\n
3.Whisk together buttermilk and egg in another bowl, then add to cornmeal mixture along with cheddar, scallion, jalapeños (to taste), and 2 tablespoons butter, stirring until just combined.\n
4.Remove pans from oven and divide remaining 2 tablespoons butter among molds. Quickly divide batter among molds (about 3 tablespoons each)and bake until tops are golden and a wooden pick or skewer comes out clean, 12 to 15 minutes (15 to 20 minutes if using skillet).\n
5.Cool corn sticks in pans on a rack 3 to 5 minutes before removing from molds. Serve warm.\n</string>
    <string name="o8">1/2 Cup Sugar\n
1 Cup Butter\n
2 Cup Flour\n
1 Egg\n
Heart shape moulds\n
200 Gram Strawberries\n
50 Gram Sugar\n
5 Gram Gelatine\n
How to Make Strawberry Jam Shortbread Biscuit\n
1.First make short bread by slowly mixing together sugar, butter and flour.\n
2.Also add an egg once it all come together to make a dough, dust some more flour and roll it flat like a chapatti. Cut it with a heart shape ring mould then take another bigger cutter to make a layer of shortbread to form boundaries.\n
3.Bake it for 180 degree for about 9 minutes .\n
\nTo prepare strawberry jam:\n\n
1.Blend strawberries and sugar together and add gelatine. Boil it until thick.\n
2.Chill the jam down and fill between heart moulds along with some generous icing of sugar on it before serving.\n</string>
    <string name="o9">1 Egg\n
1/4 tsp salt\n
1/4 tsp white pepper\n
1 cup maida\n
1/2 tsp salt\n
1 tsp red chilli powder\n
1 tsp garlic powder\n
1 tsp ginger powder\n
1 tsp onion powder\n
1 tsp oregano\n
1 tsp chillil flakes\n
1/2 tsp white pepper\n
1 tsp basil\n
6 nos chicken drumsticks\n
1/2 tsp salt\n
1/2 tsp white pepper\n
bread crumbs (as required)\n
\nHow to Make Restaurant Style Fried Chicken\n\n
1.Break an egg in a bowl and whisk thoroughly.\n
2.Add salt and white pepper to the egg. Whisk more.\n
3.Now take maida in a bowl. Add salt, red chilli powder, garlic powder ginger powder along with onion powder, oregano, chilli flakes and some more of white pepper and basil.\n
4.Mix all of it thoroughly.\n
\nFor Marination:\n\n
1.Take chicken drumsticks in a bowl.\n
2.Add salt and white pepper to the bowl. Mix well with bare hands.\n
3.Keep aside for an hour to marinate.\n
\nPrepare Chicken:\n\n
1.After marination, take chicken pieces one after another and coat it thoroughly with the spice mixture, egg mixture and bread crumbs respectively.\n
2.After coating the chicken piece, deep fry it in a hot oil pan.\n
3.Hot and crispy Restaurant Style Fried Chicken is ready to serve.\n
</string>
    <string name="o10">For Tandoori Masala:\n\n
1 tsp Coriander Seeds\n
5 Nos Green Cardamom\n
1 Sticks Cinnamon\n
1 Bay Leaf\n
3 Nos Black Cardamom\n
3 Nos Cloves\n
1 tsp Cumin Seeds\n
1/2 tsp Turmeric Powder\n
\nFor Chicken Marination:\n\n
1 Kg Chicken\n
1 tsp Salt\n
1 tsp Red Chilli Paste\n
1 tsp Ginger- Garlic Paste\n
1 tsp Mustard Oil\n
1/2 Cup Curd\n
1 tsp Peppercorn\n
1/2 tsp Chaat Masala\n
1 tsp Tandoori Masala\n
1/2 tsp Lemon Juice\n
How to Make Roasted Chicken Masala\n
\nPreparing Tandoori Masala:\n\n
1.In a pan dry roast coriander seeds, green cardamom, cinnamon, bay leaf, black cardamom, cloves, cumin seeds and turmeric powder together.\n
2.Put all these ingredients in a grinder and grind them to make masala.\n
\nFor Marinating Chicken:\n\n
1.Place chicken in a bowl.\n
2.Add salt, red chilli paste and ginger- garlic paste to it.\n
3.Now add mustard oil, curd, peppercorn, chaat masala along with tandoori masala and lemon juice.\n
4.Mix it well using your hands so that the chicken gets properly coated with the masala.\n
5.Cover the bowl with a thin transparent sheet and keep aside to marinate for about 30 minutes.\n
6.After marinating, grill the chicken for about 20 minutes at 250 degree C.\n
7.Grilling is the last task after which the chicken is ready to serve.\n
8.Serve hot the roasted chicken with generous garnishing of Chaat masala and lemon juice along with chutney and onion rings.\n

</string>

    <string name="o11">For Coriander Chutney:\n\n
1 cup coriander leaves\n
1 Green Chilli\n
1/2 tsp black salt\n
1/2 Lemon (juiced)\n
\nFor Chaat:\n\n
2-3 aloo, boiled\n
A pinch of black salt\n
A pinch of black pepper\n
A pinch of cumin powder\n
1/2 tsp chaat masala\n
1/2 tsp chilli powder\n
1 onion, chopped\n
1/2 Lemon (juiced)\n
1 tsp tamarind chutney\n
How to Make Chatpati Aloo Chaat\n
\nPrepare Coriander Chutney:\n\n
1.Take coriander leaves in a grinder.\n
2.Add green chillis and black salt.\n
3.Grind all the ingredients together.\n
4.Add lemon juice to the freshly grinded ingredients for that tangy taste.\n
5.Mix thoroughly.\n
\nPrepare Chaat:\n\n
1.Take boiled potatoes in a pan of hot oil.\n
2.Deep fry the potatoes till golden brown.\n
3.Soak oil and put the potatoes in a bowl.\n
4.Add black salt, black pepper, cumin powder, chaat masala and chilli powder.\n
5.Sprinkle some chopped onions on top of it along with juice of half a lemon.\n
6.Pour tamarind chutney and freshly made coriander chutney.\n
7.Mix all of it thoroughly to soak all of the potatoes in the spicy and tangy flavour of the spices.\n
8.Serve in the plastic bowl with toothpicks, garnished with chopped onions.\n

</string>

    <string name="o12">
1000 Gram Dark Chocolate Coverture\n
500 Gram Butter\n
200 Gram Sugar\n
10 Nos Eggs\n
1250 Gram Flour\n
25 Gram Baking Powder\n
5 Gram Salt\n
50 Gram Cocoa Powder\n
Vanilla Essence\n
\nHow to Make Chocolate Fudge Cookies\n\n
1.Cream the butter and sugar in the machine.\n
2.Add the melted chocolate and then mix together.\n
3.Add eggs and vanilla essence.\n
4.Fold the mixture with flour, salt, baking powder and cocoa powder.\n
5.Mix together with the chocolate chips. .\n
6.Roll into cylinders of 4.5 cm diameter and freeze it.\n
7.Cut the cylinder into 1 cm thick pieces and bake at 180°c for 10 min.\n
8.Serve and store in an air-tight container.\n</string>


    <string name="o13">200 gms maida\n
2 tbsp sooji\n
1 tbsp ajwain\n
1 tsp salt\n
1 tbsp oil\n
1/2 cup water\n
1 cup urad dal paste\n
1 tsp salt\n
2 potatoes, boiled\n
1/2 tsp salt\n
1 1/2 tsp red chilli powder\n
1/2 cup mixed chana\n
1/2 tsp black salt\n
1 cup yogurt\n
1 tbsp sugar\n
Cumin powder\n
Chaat Masala\n
1 tsp meethi chutney\n
1 tsp khatti chutney\n
Pomegranate\n
Sev\n
\nHow to Make Paapdi Chaat\n\n
To Prepare Papdi:\n\n
1.Take a bowl and put Maida into it. Add sooji, ajwain and salt to it.\n
2.Mix a little and then pour oil and mix more.\n
3.Now add some water and stir the ingredients to make a dough.\n
4.Roll the dough into a flat chapati.\n
5.Cut mid-size circular pieces with tiny holes, out of the flat dough and spread them separately on a plate.\n
6.Now, take a pan full of oil and deep fry these circular pieces in it.\n
7.Fry them until golden brown and crisp.\n
\nTo Prepare Bhalla:\n\n
1.Take Urad dal paste, add salt and mix well like a dough.\n
2.Take small pieces out of the dough and deep fry them in the oil.\n
3.Deep fry until golden brown.\n
4.Take them out and soak in cold water for a few minutes.\n
\nPrepare Filling:\n\n
1.Take boiled potatoes in a bowl, add salt and red chilli powder.
2.Mash them well.
3.Take a small bowl of mixed chana, add black salt to it and mix.\n
4.In another bowl, take yogurt add some sugar and mix.\n
5.Now, spread the Papdis in a plate, put the fried pieces of dough over it and spread the mashed potato and mixed chana all over the plate.\n
6.Sprinkle cumin powder and chaat masala.\n
7.A tsp each of red chilli powder, yogurt, both meethi and khatti chutney all over the plate.\n
8.Garnish with pomegranate and sev and serve.\n

</string>
    <string name="o14">400 gms boneless chicken\n
1 1/2 tbsp salt\n
4 tsp cornflour\n
2 tsp black pepper\n
1 egg\n
3 tsp soy sauce\n
3 tsp red chilli sauce\n
8-10 garlic, chopped\n
8-10 green chillies\n
2 tsp green chilli sauce\n
1 tsp vinegar\n
1 onion, chopped\n
1 capsicum, chopped\n
1 tsp black Pepper\n
1 tsp salt\n
\nHow to Make Chilli Chicken\n\n
1.Take the chicken in a bowl, add salt, cornflour, black pepper, egg, soy sauce and red chilli sauce.\n
2.Mix it well and keep it for marination for about 20 minutes.\n
3.After the marination, take out the chicken pieces and deep fry in a pan.\n
4.Deep fry the chicken until golden brown.\n
5.Now, in another pan put chopped garlic and green chillies. Stir them well.\n
6.Add the fried chicken to the pan, followed by soy sauce, green chilli sauce, vinegar, onion, capsicum, black pepper and salt.\n
7.Mix all of these together.\n
8.Serve hot.\n




</string>
    <string name="o15">1 Cup Chicken, boiled\n
2 tsp Mayonnaise\n
1 tsp Pepper\n
2 Nos Bread\n
1 Capsicum\n
1 Lettuce\n
\nHow to Make Homemade Chicken Sandwich\n\n
1.Shred small pieces of Boiled chicken in a bowl.\n
2.Add Mayonnaise and pepper in to it.\n
3.Mix it thoroughly.\n
4.Take a slice of bread and spread the mixture on it.\n
5.Now chop capsicum and lettuce in to small pieces.\n
6.Put them on the slice.\n
7.Put another slice on top of it and cut them into two.\n
8.Serve with tomato ketchup or coriander chutney.\n

</string>
    <string name="o16">1/2 Cup arhar ki daal (husked pigeon peas/yellow lentils, soaked for 5-6 hours)\n
2 tbsp vegetable oil\n
1 tsp zeera or cumin seeds\n
1 1/2 tsp salt\n
1/8 tsp heeng or asafoetida powder\n
2 tsp green chillies\n
1 tsp chilli powder\n
1 tsp khus khus or poppy seeds\n
2 tbsp tamarind pulp\n
2 tsp sugar\n
Ginger\n
Garam masala\n
Coconut\n
\nFor outer covering:\n\n
1 cup maida or refined flour
3 tbsp ghee/oil
1/4 tsp baking powder
1/2 tsp salt
Oil for deep frying
\nHow to Make Dal Kachori\n\n
1.Drain dal and grind coarsely.\n
2.Heat oil and add jeera. When it splutters, add ginger, heeng, green chillies and saute till the color changes a bit.\n
3.Add dal, salt, garam masala, chilli powder, khus khus, coconut and saute till its fried. Add about 1/4 cup water and cook till dal is cooked through. Mix in the tamarind and sugar and keep aside.\n
4.Mix baking powder and salt into the maida. Rub ghee/oil into the maida, add water and knead into stiff dough. Rest, cover for 15 minutes.\n
5.Make walnut sized rounds of the dal mixture.\n
6.Break pieces of dough and roll into walnut sized rounds. Roll these flat into 1/4 inch rounds and pinch about 1/2 of the edge all around, leaving the centre thicker.\n
7.Now wet the pressed edges, and place a ball of the filling in the centre. Bring the wet edges together, covering the filling completely, and pinch together to seal.\n
8.Heat oil and deep-fry the kachoris, first over high heat, then over medium heat so that it cooks through, and browns evenly.\n</string>
    <string name="o17">1 Kg chicken wings\n
1 Tbsp chilli garlic paste\n
2 Tbsp soy sauce\n
2 Tbsp tamarind puree\n
2 Tbsp ginger minced\n
1/2 Cup vinegar\n
1 Tbsp jaggery or honey\n
1 Tbsp black pepper\n
2 Tbsp lemon juice\n
1 Cup flour\n
1 Cup corn starch\n
3 Tbsp oil ( to bake) or fry\n
\nHow to Make Sticky Tamarind Chicken Wings\n\n
1.First wash and pat dry the chicken wings.\n
2.Make a marinade using soy sauce, tamarind puree, garlic pasta, some ginger, vinegar, lemon juice, flour and corn starch.\n
3.Pour over the chicken wings and marinate for 2 hours.\n
4.Either you can bake the chicken wings in an oven for 30 minutes at 180C or alternatively fry it in a kadhai or in a heavy bottomed pan until golden brown and crispy.\n</string>
    <string name="o18">3 cups maida / refined flour\n
1 tsp salt\n
2 cups unsalted butter\n
1 cup iced water\n
1 kg mixed vegetables-chopped fine, and cooked\n
1 cup onion-chopped fine\n
2 Tbsp butter\n
1 tsp salt\n
1 Tbsp dhania powder\n
1 tsp garam masala\n
1 tsp amchoor\n
1 tsp chilli powder or to taste\n
1 tsp pissi kali mirch\n
egg yolk-mixed with 2 Tbsp milk for brushing or just milk\n
\nHow to Make Vegetable Patties\n\n
1.For dough\n
2.Mix maida, salt and 1 cup butter into a crumbly consistency.\n
3.Add 1 the water and continue to mix into a crumbly mixture. Add some more water till no dry particles remain.\n
4.Cover in plastic wrap and refrigerate for 1 hour or so.\n
5.Beat the butter into a 6" square between two sheets of plastic.\n
6.Roll the dough into a rectangle 12"x 26".\n
7.Place butter in center and fold first one end over, then the other.\n
8.Press edges to seal and refrigerate for 15 minutes.\n
9.Roll dough into a long strip again, fold one third from one end towards center and then the other. Chill. And repeat twice more before using as required.\n
\nFor stuffing:\n\n
1.Heat butter and add onions when butter melts.\n
2.Saute till onions are a little soft. Add vegetables, salt, dhania, garam masala, amchoor, chilli powder and pissi kali mirch and stir-fry till well mixed.\n
3.Roll dough 1" thick, cut into rectangles.\n
4.Wet edges, place the mixture in one half and fold over. Press to seal.\n
5.Brush top with egg yolk mixture and bake in a hot oven 425 F-200C for 15 to 20 minutes.\n</string>
    <string name="o19">1 Cup Finger millet flour\n
1/4 Cup Jaggery, powdered\n
1/4 Cup Peanuts, roasted\n
1/4 Cup Coconut, grated\n
A pinch of Salt\n
\nHow to Make Coconut Ladoo (Laddu)\n\
1.Take the flour and salt in a bowl and sprinkle water little by little whilst mixing it but breaking them into crumbs as you keep mixing.\n
2.Mix in the coconut. Steam the mixture with coconut for 10-15 minutes.\n
3.Lay the mixture onto a tray and let it cool.\n
4.Blend the jaggery with the flour mixture and peanuts.\n
5.Roll them into lemon-sized balls and devour!\n</string>
    <string name="o20">250 gms mutton mince\n
1 tsp ginger paste\n
1 tsp garlic paste\n
1 Green chilli (coarsely ground)\n
1/2 tsp turmeric\n
1 tsp red chilli powder\n
1/2 tsp clove-cinnamon powder\n
2 tbsp potatoes (mashed), boiled\n
5-6 pudina leaves, finely chopped\n
1 tbsp coriander, chopped\n
to taste salt\n
Bread crumbs (to coat)\n
4 Eggs (whisked, to coat the cutlets)\n
Oil (to deep fry)\n
\nHow to Make Parsi Mutton Cutlets\n\n
1.In a bowl take the mince and massage it with your hands for 3-4 minutes.\n
2.Now add the ginger paste, garlic paste, green chilli, turmeric, red chilli powder, clove-cinnamon powder, mashed potato, pudina, dhaniya and salt. Mix it well.\n
3.Make medium sized round patties (makes around 5-6). Coat the cutlets with bread crumbs from both sides. Refrigerate for 30 minutes.\n
4.Whisk eggs. Coat the refrigerated cutlets in the egg mixture. Deep fry in hot oil till golden brown from both sides.\n
5.Serve with sliced onions and chutney. Squeeze some lemon juice on top if you want.\n</string>


</resources>
